<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://aaronfs07.github.io/rssfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>Aaron's RSS Feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-27T12:34:19.509Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://aaronfs07.github.io/rssfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://aaronfs07.github.io/rssfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanded Data Volume with Checkpoints - Options?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpf1dr/expanded_data_volume_with_checkpoints_options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpf1dr/expanded_data_volume_with_checkpoints_options/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T12:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expanded Data Volume with Checkpoints - Options?
 I was an idiot and expanded my data drive (does not contain the OS) on a VM that had checkpoints in place from a few days prior.
 The server was shutdown at the time and came back online just fine. The data volume is operating fine and nothing seems out of place from a user experience perspective. That's the good news, nothing bad has happened yet..
 However, what are my options now? The OS does not see the newly allocated disk space if relevant.
 The main VHDX is 13.5 TB (this is the one I expanded), the AVHDX is 419 GB, and there is 829 GB free on the drive that contains them both so there should be enough space to merge them.
 We do have VEEAM backups both onsite and in the cloud, but obviously 13.5 TB is a doozy even over the LAN.
 The checkpoint is from 9/20, the expansion was on 9/24, and the time of this posting is 9/27.
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/neuroticelite  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does anyone use Uniflow Online Express?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpeqfp/does_anyone_use_uniflow_online_express/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpeqfp/does_anyone_use_uniflow_online_express/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does anyone have any experience with this? Client was sold a new printer by Canon without talking to us and they were told nothing would change. They were using ULM which integrates to their AD. It appears that ULM is no longer supported and Canon told the client they will need to use Uniflow Online Express which I believe is the free tier of Uniflow. 
 I'm really struggling to find anything on the Canon site about the technical details, it's mostly just sales stuff. From my understanding so far it won't link with AD, that would be the paid for uniflow version which would also need the paid for Universal Print by Microsoft (which uses Azure AD rather then AD). 
 I think the bit I'm hazy on is how it all connects. Does the Uniflow driver connect to something in the cloud that connects to the printer?
 Going forwards it's not essential that it integrates with AD, it's a small school with 60 - 70 staff, so I could set them individually and add it to the new user process, but I curious as to peoples experiances. 
    submitted by    /u/Logical_Strain_6165  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXO - send mails to external recipients with delay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpegx2/exo_send_mails_to_external_recipients_with_delay/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpegx2/exo_send_mails_to_external_recipients_with_delay/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title says it all: is it possible to delay e-mails that get sent to an external recipient with a slight delay?
 We're using a third-party tool to attach our internal and external mail signatures. The tool also attaches the signature to the mail within the senders' outbox, but it uses the signature of the last email sent.
 That's our Problem. For legal reasons, we need to always attach the external signature within the senders' outbox.
 As the tool doesn't provide this feature, it would be helpful to delay the mail to the external recipient for a few seconds, so the signature would be our external signature. 
 ​
 Is this possible with exchange online, or is there a better solution?
 ​
 Here is a diagram of the current mailflow: 805-1.png (925×515) (codetwo.com)
    submitted by    /u/VariousLawyer4183  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Certificates to start my way in the business as an apprentice?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpe9we/certificates_to_start_my_way_in_the_business_as/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpe9we/certificates_to_start_my_way_in_the_business_as/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everybody,
 I'm currently doing an apprenticeship as a sysadmin in Switzerland and I'm wondering if you guys could tell me what useful certificates I could get to start in this business. I feel like I don't get enough training in my apprenticeship that's why I want to get some certificates so I'll have a better chance of finding a good job after my apprenticeship.
 Some certificates that are currently on my mind are MS-700 Teams Administrator Associate, AZ-104 Azure Administrator Associate, and the Cisco CCNA. What are your thoughts? 
 ​
 Thanks for any help.
    submitted by    /u/WandiWasTaken  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing File Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpe6yj/managing_file_servers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpe6yj/managing_file_servers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the title implies, i'm getting frustrated with our Windows file servers
 The cost of storage has our IT Service continuously fighting over the usage of this said storage.
 I have several scripts running to clean old data that haven't been modified/accessed in years.
 But once you get to that infamous 260 character limitation, things become quite tedious. One liner PS scripts become a mix of special functions to "bypass" the character limit, exporting data into csv changing the format of the paths, and reimporting everything back. Untill you realise that a special character such as " [ ] " cannot be processed.
 My users have the bad habit of creating path folders as if they were writing an encyclopedia, no effort whatsoever is put in keeping path folders short.
 I have paths where you ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How would a network be blocking vpns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpdwj3/how_would_a_network_be_blocking_vpns/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpdwj3/how_would_a_network_be_blocking_vpns/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:18:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My school have a smooth wall firewall and i assume are using dpi however i was required to download a root ssl certificate which i have deleted because of security risks involved with root certs. Without these certs some sites don’t load because of not being able to establish a https connection. I have pritunl vpn in a vm on a server and it accessible through port 17905 which i don’t think is a standard port if i use obfuscation would the vpn work and get past the firewall or because i don’t have the ssl cert downloaded would that stop me connecting. Does anyone have an idea of what part either the ssl cert or dpi is blocking i also noted that you can’t seem to connect to IP’s directly as in i couldn’t connect to the vpns webpage even though i port forwarded it though i could connect to websites that i reverse looked up to find there ip The vpn works when on any other network including 4g(on iPhone) Is this just a easy case to finding a vpn that supports obfuscation to bypass the dpi? Thank you
    submitted by    /u/redisgoodboy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible to configure brand new Cisco switches/routers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpdu29/ansible_to_configure_brand_new_cisco/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpdu29/ansible_to_configure_brand_new_cisco/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello all. 
 I was at a conference the other day and saw that Cisco DNAC can adopt and provision brand new switches / routers without needing telnet/ssh first.
 From what I understand they are using DHCP Option 43 to point devices to DNAC but also mentioned using the g0/0/0 OOB port. Is this possible with Ansible? I would hate to have to login to XXX brand devices just to get Ansible reach ability for configuration.
 Im also open to any other product if you all have any ideas.
 Thank you
    submitted by    /u/ds-unraid  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to check if urls are using google analytics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpdj6o/how_to_check_if_urls_are_using_google_analytics/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpdj6o/how_to_check_if_urls_are_using_google_analytics/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the "recent" rulings from more and more data protection authorities regarding the legality of using Google analytics as a European company - it has finally become a priority for us to get a proper overview. 
 Our "known" offenders have been working on this for a while preparing pseudonymization or moving away from GA, but as we have 400+ domains each with the option of subdomains I'm sure we have more around which have come in over the years from M&As or simply rogue employees. 
 As we have a pretty good overview of the domains I'm looking for a simple way to scan a list of hostnames and produce a GA "Yes/no" result. 
 I considered just doing an invoke-webrequest and checking for references to GA .js files such as 
  
Google Analytics (ga.js)
 Google Analytics Remarketing (dc.js)
 Google Universal Analytics (analytics.js)
 Google Analytics Global Site Tag (gtag.js)
 Google Analytics Experiments (ga_exp.js)
 Google Tag Manager (gtm.js)
 Google AdWords Conversion (conversion.js)
 Google AdWords Phone Conversion (loader.js)
 Google AdWords Remarketing (conversion.js)
 Google AdWords Dynamic Remarketing (conversion.js)
  
I'm not really sure if that would produce valid results 
 surely someone else has already come across this, or produced a script which my google-fu is just not able to dig out 
 I've looked at sites such as builtwith.com or gachecker.com - but can't run through 1000s of hostnames by hand
    submitted by    /u/H-Bernhard  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MS Support says it can be done but someone here might be able to]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpd8d5/ms_support_says_it_can_be_done_but_someone_here/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpd8d5/ms_support_says_it_can_be_done_but_someone_here/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T10:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi awesome Sys admins. I have an exo mailbox that sends on behalf of some users from a web server. I would like to know if there is a way to allow only the web server to send on behalf of these users. Eg. mailbox [webserver@domain.com](mailto:webserver@domain.com) sends and email to client coming from [user1@domain.com](mailto:user1@domain.com). I would like that [webserver@domain.com](mailto:webserver@domain.com) can only send on behalf of [user1@domain.com](mailto:user1@domain.com) from IP 1.1.1.1. 
 Microsoft support guy says its not possible but im sure someone here knows of a way.
    submitted by    /u/SignificanceFair3298  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you having issues with OneDrive for Business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpcyzi/are_you_having_issues_with_onedrive_for_business/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpcyzi/are_you_having_issues_with_onedrive_for_business/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T10:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi
 Over the last few days we are starting to see users having issues with onedrive for business.
 The Onedrive client will either hang at "processing changes..." of "We are trying to sign you in" 
 We also see that the client removes synced folders from explorer, and when we try to sync them it prompts a message saying "We found this folder, would you like to use this" 
 More and more users are having general issues with Onedrive, are you guys seeing something similar?
    submitted by    /u/PullingCables  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How stupid are your NOC?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpcwwa/how_stupid_are_your_noc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpcwwa/how_stupid_are_your_noc/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T10:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have to point out really obvious stuff to our NOC, like “check the component field” of an alert so you understand what is alerting.
 Is this normal? It happens all the time and theyve been trained up on the platform.
 I’m not sure how high of a standard a NOC usually is.
    submitted by    /u/sysadmincrazy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage Chrome Enterprise Browsers per user or per device]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpcoha/manage_chrome_enterprise_browsers_per_user_or_per/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpcoha/manage_chrome_enterprise_browsers_per_user_or_per/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T10:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi
 New to the Chrome Enterprise world and still trying to understand how the admin console and management process works there. 
 It seems like I can apply settings only to organizational units. That has raised 3 questions:
  
Is that accurate? That's the only segmentation I have? 
 Can I apply a setting to a specific user or a machine? 
 What happens if I apply two conflicting settings to two different organizational units, and one user from OU1 logins to a browser used previously by a user from OU2?
  
   submitted by    /u/dodin33359  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[spanning tree loop mitigation suggestions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpcbqp/spanning_tree_loop_mitigation_suggestions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpcbqp/spanning_tree_loop_mitigation_suggestions/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[good morning,
 other than storm control and using trill, what tech, settings, 3rd party solutions can i use to mitigate loop storms?
 thank you
    submitted by    /u/garcetto  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneDrive GPO issues having]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpc45u/onedrive_gpo_issues_having/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpc45u/onedrive_gpo_issues_having/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi gents,
 ​
 I have an question for you, and hopefully someone can help me out. 
 ​
 I am trying to get the proper GPO's enabled for our OneDrive environment. 
 But here is the problem
 ​
  
when i go to \\domain\sysvol\domain\policy , first issue there is no map called PolicyDefinitions.
 When i create the folder PolicyDefinitions in that root, and i copy the adml admx files in that new created folder.
 In GPOeditor under computer/administrative settings only having the OneDrive settings. But when i remove that folder the old settings are back, really strange.
  
anyone who can help me out?
    submitted by    /u/testlab01  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have moments when you literally have nothing to do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpbxhe/do_you_have_moments_when_you_literally_have/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpbxhe/do_you_have_moments_when_you_literally_have/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've started doing my apprenticeship program (Ausbuildung in German) in a medium jewelry manufacturer as system administrator. And most of the time there is always something to do. Someone's PC won't boot, we need to install or configure smth, etc. But sometimes there is literally nothing to do, and I just sit there doing basically nothing. Of course I am not doing all the tasks since I am only a trainee, so I wanted to ask if that also happens to you.
    submitted by    /u/_Rev1k_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VXLAN Issue | Remote vtep vxlan does not receive the mac address?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpbom7/vxlan_issue_remote_vtep_vxlan_does_not_receive/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpbom7/vxlan_issue_remote_vtep_vxlan_does_not_receive/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm having trouble installing or receiving any mac address that the remote VTEP sent. I have verified that both the tunnel and the l2vpn/evpn connection are operational. I have two questions on this matter.
  
Is this issue related to RD/RT or on how I import the routes ? Here's the configuration and setup. 
  
Topology: https://ibb.co/p1Wcsf3
 NX-01# show l2route evpn mac all Flags -(Rmac):Router MAC (Stt):Static (L):Local (R):Remote (V):vPC link (Dup):Duplicate (Spl):Split (Rcv):Recv (AD):Auto-Delete (D):Del Pending (S):Stale (C):Clear, (Ps):Peer Sync (O):Re-Originated (Nho):NH-Override (Pf):Permanently-Frozen Topology Mac Address Prod Flags Seq No Next-Hops ----------- -------------- ------ ------------- ---------- ---------------- 11 aabb.cc80.3000 Local L, 0 Eth1/2 22 aabb.cc80.3000 L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Realize Operations EPOps agent vs Zabbix for windows monitoring.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpbiau/vmware_realize_operations_epops_agent_vs_zabbix/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpbiau/vmware_realize_operations_epops_agent_vs_zabbix/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ChadThunderPenis97  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Companies that provide short/long term MacBook rentals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpbgo9/companies_that_provide_shortlong_term_macbook/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpbgo9/companies_that_provide_shortlong_term_macbook/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T09:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work for a fully remote company that has employees in the US/UK/a few other countries and we're looking for a vendor that can supply MacBooks in at the very least, the US or UK.
 Does anyone have any recommendations? I've been searching for a while and can't find any places that tick all the boxes for us.
 The main requirements are: * Up-to-date MacBook hardware options * Same day swap out service when a device is faulty * Short and long term (2+ year) rentals (mostly long term)
    submitted by    /u/lostsparekeys  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluating Email Security solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpaz8q/evaluating_email_security_solutions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpaz8q/evaluating_email_security_solutions/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:39:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello all.
 We were currently evaluating some email security solutions.
 We evaluated Proofpoint Security Essentials and Anubis Networks.
 Both are very good, however, meanwhile we also acquired Office 365 E5 licenses for all users, and thus, we were able to test Microsoft Defender for Office 365.
 So I'm asking your opinion, if I should spend money on Proofpoint (therefore having 2 products Proofpoint SE + Defender) or if Microsoft Defender for Office 365 will be enough to stop those pesky emails (spam, phishing, malware).
 Thank you for your opinions.
    submitted by    /u/thomasdarko  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Site mode List for IP Ranges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpayvi/enterprise_site_mode_list_for_ip_ranges/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpayvi/enterprise_site_mode_list_for_ip_ranges/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the death of IE, I have been given the task of somehow putting a bunch of /16 ranges into Enterprise Site Mode so some ancient tech can still be used.
 This is because the tech uses TLS 1.0, which is now no longer supported in Edge. So we have to use Enterprise Mode.
 The documentation seems to indicate that there are NO wildcard options for Enterprise Site Mode, but will something like putting: '10.48' allow all subsequent addresses?
    submitted by    /u/MagicPracticalFlame  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco SD-Wan Vlan Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpaw0p/cisco_sdwan_vlan_creation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpaw0p/cisco_sdwan_vlan_creation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello all , i am currently migrating for a customer to deploy cisco sd-wan across all the sites.
 While doing so migrating for the datacenters i had no issues at all , but while migrating for the braches i faced a little issue with the Vlan creation on the Cisco Vmanage.
 as i do usally i first check the router configuration that is currently deployed on the site and then create template on the cisco vmanage for the sd-wan router thats going to replace it, while all the brached on the customer side are router on stick which means all the vlans are created on the router it self and there is no core switch or any kind of L3 switch on the braches.
 The only issue that i am facing is that the customer has total of 94 different vlans on each branch , so the questions is do i create 94 different vlan template and push it ? , which i already did and was stuck at about 30 and i cannot put any more on VPN 1 (service side vpn) , or is this another way or solution that i am not awre about ? 
 appreciate any help or advice
    submitted by    /u/redxify95  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tons of event id 4625 - common fixes not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpap63/tons_of_event_id_4625_common_fixes_not_working/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpap63/tons_of_event_id_4625_common_fixes_not_working/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello fellow sysadmins!
 After being a long-time lurker in this subreddit its my first time posting here! :)
 Being employed by an MSP, there is currently an issue with a few devices getting hammered by login attempts causing 4625 - unknown username or password events. The issue persists since a few weeks without being able to find a solution.
 <EventID>4625</EventID> <Version>0</Version> <Level>0</Level> <Task>12544</Task> <Opcode>0</Opcode> <Keywords>0x8010000000000000</Keywords> <TimeCreated SystemTime="2022-08-31T10:15:21.422755100Z" /> <EventRecordID>265607696</EventRecordID> <Correlation ActivityID="{B32A7C79-ACD6-0000-9F7C-2AB3D6ACD801}" /> <Execution ProcessID="744" ThreadID="82036" /> <Channel>Security</Channel> <Computer>Server.domain.local/Computer> <Security /> </System> - <Eve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need firmware for iPoMan II 1201 v1.12 or v2.xx]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpamh1/need_firmware_for_ipoman_ii_1201_v112_or_v2xx/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpamh1/need_firmware_for_ipoman_ii_1201_v112_or_v2xx/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T08:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anybody has this firmware stored somewhere?
 The PDU is old, but I used it still in my personal network.
 However the current version has small glitches and locks up every few weeks. 
 So maybe someone has firmware for the iPoMan II 1201 v1.12 or v2.xx even. Thanks in advance.
    submitted by    /u/HHawk79  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell switch N2000 incorrect mac address]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpaa2d/dell_switch_n2000_incorrect_mac_address/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xpaa2d/dell_switch_n2000_incorrect_mac_address/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T07:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I am running ‘show arp’ that gives me the MAC address of a device I am after, I am trying to see what port this device is connected to, to retrieve this information I use ‘show mac address-table’ however, the MAC address returned is completely different. 
 Anyone know why this is? I physically plugged directly into my port 27 on the dell switch of the known device and the MAC address from the table is still wrong but arp is showing the correct MAC address. I also tried clearing the MAC address table with no luck. The dell switch is running firmware 6.6.3.6
    submitted by    /u/Affectionate-Time86  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Full Access" permissions on a mailbox will also display private items?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpa1a5/full_access_permissions_on_a_mailbox_will_also/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpa1a5/full_access_permissions_on_a_mailbox_will_also/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T07:42:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So today we discovered a rather worrying issue when it was reported that someone (User A) was able to see private appointments in User B's calendar when they shouldn't have been able to.
 Cue digging around in the calendar permissions and delegates to see how this could have happened but no where did User A have any such permission.
 Eventually we found that they were in a group that had been given full access to User B's mailbox, however previously this has never been an issue and the permissions have been in place for quite some time. As a test, we removed the group from Full Access and half an hour later, User A couldn't see private items anymore.
 I can't find anything online (feel free to perform better Google-fu) that suggests that MS have made this change and our mailboxes were migrated to EO a few years ago and there haven't been any recent changes that we've made. Has anyone else encountered this recently?
    submitted by    /u/vade__retro  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strange TRAEFIK certificate warning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpa12c/strange_traefik_certificate_warning/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xpa12c/strange_traefik_certificate_warning/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T07:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good day to all my fellow sysadmins!
 I am once again asking for your technical support.
 I have a very strange case of "tries to connect to something other, than what I want it to" with outlook, or more precisely, an add-in, which doesn't have a lot to do with the service, it tries to get the certificate from.
 Let me try and explain, as I am a total newbie, when it comes to certs:
 My client has MailStore installed on-premise and the add-in activated for his outlook installation. When opening Outlook, with the add-in, a cert warning pops up, asking, if I trust this website/ connection. When I look at the cert, I see "TRAEFIK DEFAULT CERT" as the issuer. Now, I've looked up the name, and it seems to be a trustworthy service of some sort, but again, it has nothing to do with our MailStore …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAs in Asia, how are you dealing with services which also have presence in Hong Kong and potentially route/ DNS direct there?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp9di0/sas_in_asia_how_are_you_dealing_with_services/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp9di0/sas_in_asia_how_are_you_dealing_with_services/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T07:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if traffic itself can be blocked, DNS resolution is a sticking point. Someone must have tried to tackle this already but I can't find any good leads. Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/C3PU  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from MSP to In-House IT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp6qya/migrating_from_msp_to_inhouse_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp6qya/migrating_from_msp_to_inhouse_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T04:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I’ve recently got a new job at a company to migrate from their current MSP to lead the in house IT department, and eventually phase them out.
 We have been back and forth with them and they have let us know that they can’t provide any access to anything before signing an indemnity clause (which is fair enough).
 We are sorting out the new agreement where they are asking which services to drop for now and to change to a block hour rate service instead.
 They run RMM software as usual, and are asking if we want to adopt it with a fee. Are there any better solutions for a small business instead of RMM? Monitoring/Management more tailored for in-house IT?
 Any other advice from people who have maybe dealt with this situation before will be appreciated as well.
 Apologies if not enough detail, first time posting.
    submitted by    /u/Due_Captain_5555  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is now a good time for job change.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp49yx/is_now_a_good_time_for_job_change/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp49yx/is_now_a_good_time_for_job_change/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T02:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is now a good time for job change given the fact that we are heading into a recession. 
 I have been working as a system administrator for the last 12 yrs.(mostly onprem infra and Azure for AD). I have recently passed AWS SAA C02, CKA. I have gone thru some courses on Ansible, jenkins, Terraform, Python to understand all the moving pieces in the world of DevOps. I have done some small projects at my home lab to get an understanding of these technologies. 
 I have started looking at the job market this month and started noticing very few postings. (I am based in Canada, looking for opportunities in US and Canada). 
 I spoke to few of my friends and colleagues who are in the industry and i have got mixed opinions. Some say, DevOps job roles won't be affected even if we end up in a recession. Some say, just stick to my current job (stable job) until the dust settles. 
 I m really confused of what to do. Should i wait until early next year or should I continue with my job search. 
 Please advise.
    submitted by    /u/kkt_98  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does the RSRP gets calculated in a device?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xp3d9l/how_does_the_rsrp_gets_calculated_in_a_device/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xp3d9l/how_does_the_rsrp_gets_calculated_in_a_device/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T02:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 If my question is surprisingly simple for you, it is because my background is not in telecommunication. I'm a machine learning engineer. But for a project, I need to understand the environment very well.
 I'm learning about the handover and resource allocation in telecommunication. The handover is not the main part actually. But because transferring devices get triggered by devices' measurement reports, I need to understand it in the context of 5G.
 The problem is 3GPP standards and ETSI are generic and don't talk about what happens in devices exactly. Online websites that talk about it contradict each other.
 So I'm wondering if someone can point me to a document that explains exactly what happens in a mobile device before sending those measurement reports.
 Thanks,
    submitted by    /u/curly_crazy_curious  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it time to leave IT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp26mh/is_it_time_to_leave_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xp26mh/is_it_time_to_leave_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T01:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seriously wondering if it’s time to leave IT as a profession. I’m finding it more and more difficult to keep up with the changes and increased complexity and no longer find any joy in learning new stuff. Honestly to the point I dread upgrades because it always breaks stuff and takes a ton of ky time. I have absolutely no desire to go into project management or sales, so that’s obviously not a career direction.
    submitted by    /u/craigers21  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrueNAS Scale 22.02.3 Review: What Works Well and What Needs Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-_cQa7npg_A</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-_cQa7npg_A"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T00:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ring to Star Topology Migration Layer3 Switch vs Router]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xp0ig2/ring_to_star_topology_migration_layer3_switch_vs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xp0ig2/ring_to_star_topology_migration_layer3_switch_vs/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-27T00:07:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I manage a 40G ring network with around 10 locations. Each location has around 20 routes. Each site is using a Juniper EX4300 pair connected to an OSPF ring. Our DC sits on the ring and aggregates all routes with a pair of EX4600s. Our firewall then does peering and WAN. 
 We are in the process of migrating from a ring topology to a star topology in a new colocation space. I am looking for advice on hardware. Each location will be connected to the DC w/ 2 x 10G fiber strands and 1G WISP backup. 
 I am thinking of dropping 2 x MX150s at each location, and then using an ACX 7024 pair at the DC, but is this overkill? Should I just upgrade to a better L3 switch setup? Looking for recommendations. I love Juniper but am open to other options. I am pretty familiar w/ Cisco IOS and other similar platforms. We are somewhat budget oriented, but I am trying to stay away from Mikrotik. (We are required to have support contracts)
 I have never working with the MX or ACX series before. I was considering the MX204, but with the EoL announcement, it is out of the question. We are looking to purchase hardware early next year, and it will probably be another year after that until the project is complete. Thank you
    submitted by    /u/prodigydeadi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Office 365 users not receiving external emails to alias]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoyb14/office_365_users_not_receiving_external_emails_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoyb14/office_365_users_not_receiving_external_emails_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T22:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using M365 Business Standard with verified domain (4+ years).
  
The problem is with both Outlook OWA and desktop.
 Users are not able to receive external emails to their aliases.
 Emails not going to spam or junk.
 I have verified with the MS email tools that email flow is working.
 I thought adding an alias was pretty straightforward, but just to be on the safe side I have removed and then re-added the aliases following MS KB to the letter.
  
Am I doing something wrong?
 ​
 EDIT: Okay, so now I feel like an ID10T *facepalm*
 The specific user I was testing on had well over 100 rules setup... Yep, one was blocking. Not sure which, though, so I will have to go through them with her.
    submitted by    /u/YesImThatJ  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For those with MacOS users, or using it yourself, how are you persistently mounting Samba network shares?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xowdvt/for_those_with_macos_users_or_using_it_yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xowdvt/for_those_with_macos_users_or_using_it_yourself/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T21:24:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm actually asking for home use (hence my lack of expertise, and my hacky solution shown below), but was wondering if there was a more correct way to achieve this.
 On the web the commonly suggested method seems to be to add the share in Login Items.
 This works initially but as it just fires at login and doesn't keep alive through disruptions, the user will have to reconnect manually through Finder again should the connection drop.
 Were I on Linux I would just use fstab, but I'm seeing some conflicting information on this for MacOS and Samba network shares.
 It varies from using similar files in the form of "/etc/auto_master", "/etc/auto_smb", "synthetic.conf", and then of course "/etc/fstab" itself (which itself has further different suggestions to use "cifs" in the filesystem type column, or "-fstype=smbfs" in the options column).
 What is the best, and most "correct" approach as of Monterrey, which will ensure if the connection drops, the mount will work again upon reconnection?
  
Hacky (albeit working) solution.
 Launchctl file in /Library/LaunchDaemons.
 <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> <!DOCTYPE plist PUBLIC "-//Apple//DTD PLIST 1.0//EN" "http://www.apple.com/DTDs/PropertyList-1.0.dtd"> <plist version="1.0"> <dict> <key>Label</key> <string>org.obfuscated.name</string> <key>Program</key> <string>/Users/obfuscated/mount.sh</string> <key>StartInterval</key> <integer>2</integer> <key>ThrottleInterval</key> <integer>0</integer> </dict> </plist> 
 mount.sh
 #!/bin/bash if ! (df -h | grep /Users/obfuscated/mountDir); then mount -t smbfs //guest@192.168.0.242/MediaGuest /Users/obfuscated/mountDir fi 
    submitted by    /u/AlwynEvokedHippest  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WiFi at a Large Summer Camp - Brand New Cabins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xovox4/wifi_at_a_large_summer_camp_brand_new_cabins/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xovox4/wifi_at_a_large_summer_camp_brand_new_cabins/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted to get some people's opinions on an affordable but robust way to connect new cabins (sleeps 12 in bunks) at a summer camp. Because it will be new construction we'll have more options in terms of cable runs and infrastructure. As we are a nonprofit, cost is always a concern and has to be balanced with performance. We currently use mostly Ubiquiti gear for better or for worse and have 500mb fiber coming in with internal fiber to most developed "areas" of our 1000 acre campus.
 My initial thought was running fiber from one of our main hubs to the central bath house, where a fiber switch would feed fiber directly to each of the cabins. In the cabins' attic would be a media converter and access point. I'm thinking I'd like to get some ethernet drops run into convenient places and have the ability to upgrade to a fiber switch if more connections become a need late on.
 Thoughts or suggestions?
    submitted by    /u/Substantial-Coach827  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What horrifying IT experiences have you had?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xou4f0/what_horrifying_it_experiences_have_you_had/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xou4f0/what_horrifying_it_experiences_have_you_had/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello /r/sysadmin... Meredith and JJ at PDQ here. We're compiling material for a spoooky seasonal post, and with Halloween right around the corner, what's more terrifying than Tales From IT? We'd like to hear your aggravating, disturbing, and/or truly terrifying IT experiences. Narcissistic nepotistic nagging user you were forced to do personal work for? Boss from the 7th circle of Hades? Supporting tech devices older than your parents? All scary stories are welcome.
 If forms are your fancy, we've got one for you, https://forms.office.com/r/ArD9m6a7Q6
 If not, leave your story in the comments below.
    submitted by    /u/PDQit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things to look out for in Aruba wireless vs Cisco?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xou22c/things_to_look_out_for_in_aruba_wireless_vs_cisco/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xou22c/things_to_look_out_for_in_aruba_wireless_vs_cisco/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T20:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi All,
 I've been working almost exclusively with Cisco wireless over last few years (some Meraki thrown in for good measure). This includes ekahau surveys, deployment, troubleshooting a range of AirOS and the new Catalyst WLCs, across hundreds of deployments at this stage. 
 I have an upcoming opportunity to start working with Aruba wireless side of things (due to costs, lead times in some areas, general boredom, proof of concept), which I have not touched in years. Generally I would say a wireless protocol is a wireless protocol, regardless of vendor - However, based on your experiences, is there any glaring differences or "gotchas" when it comes to switching from deploying cisco 5508/5520/9800s to the Aruba equivalents? I would love to hear some personal experiences from others making a similar switch, and how that went.
    submitted by    /u/Draezy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Painters are idiots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xotr97/painters_are_idiots/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xotr97/painters_are_idiots/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T19:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So we had some fun at work today. First some background - we are an industrial manufacturing company, and our head office is on the same premises as our factory. Our primary server room shares a wall with the raw materials warehouse. Don't ask, we're working on changing this.
 ​
 This morning I go into the server room to get a serial number off a device, and I notice a puddle of water on the floor. Fortunately all servers are in racks and are lifted well off the floor, so no equipment is in immediate danger. We immediately call facilities to come and take a look and while we wait, we trace the water to a leak in the drain leading from one of the air conditioners. Now while this was cracked, it shouldn't be leaking this much, as it drains outside of the room. 
 ​
 Facilities hooks up a temp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSP reading my emails?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoshsf/msp_reading_my_emails/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoshsf/msp_reading_my_emails/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T19:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR: I suspect that the CEO of our MSP is reading my (confidential) emails. How can I prove it?
 Longer version:
 I work for a small company with 120 users. I am in charge of the administrative departments, including IT. We have a dedicated IT staff of 2; they do most of the heavy lifting regarding the day to day admin stuff and helpdesk. We use our MSP for infrastructure and M365 administration including exchange online.
 We have been working with them for 1.5 years now. In the last few months some issues have come up regarding their adherence to SLAs. Plus we are currently negotiating new server equipment (they are one possible vendor amongst others).
 During these discussions their CEO has confronted me with some arguments about which I am unsure how he might have obtained them.
 Exam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you guys respond to people passing around cyber security themed clickbait articles?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xorfbd/how_do_you_guys_respond_to_people_passing_around/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xorfbd/how_do_you_guys_respond_to_people_passing_around/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T18:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have a few users that will occasionally post some pretty dubious technology or security related articles to some of the company teams channels. It's pretty annoying, and I often need to get in there and refute something, or point out how it doesn't apply to our situation.
 I'm talking about people tagging IT and saying that we need to turn off windows updates ASAP, with a link to an article titled "Microsoft confirms it's intentionally bricking 3rd party laptops" (I'm paraphrasing the title) . The actual article is wildly misleading, and appears to be a reference to a problem with a windows update that happened several years ago.
 Also got a "Looks like we can stop using MFA?" comment in reference to an article with a title like "MFA does nothing!". This one was native marketing for a privacy VPN product. The argument was basically that MFA doesn't stop your employer from monitoring your web traffic, technically correct, but misses the whole point of MFA.
 Do you guys have a ready response when people post stuff like this? If it's a security vulnerability thing, I see if there is a CVE reference, if it's an MS thing, a KB. with those it's possible to actually check if this is a real thing we have to care about, but it basically never is.
    submitted by    /u/DJDoubleDave  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco 4507R+E Sup8e Redundant Supervisor 10GB Ports Active]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xorbre/cisco_4507re_sup8e_redundant_supervisor_10gb/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xorbre/cisco_4507re_sup8e_redundant_supervisor_10gb/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T18:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Guys,
 I have a quick question on a Cisco Core 4507 with Redundant Supervisors (WS‑X45-Sup8-E) on how many of the 10GB ports are active when the Supervisors are in Redundant Mode. With the Supervisor 7E when the supervisors are in Redundant Mode only 1 of 10GB ports are active and the other three ports (2 i know are 1GB) seem to be disabled. I am trying to figure out if we would see the same behavior with the Sup8 as well
    submitted by    /u/Not_A_Psyic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samba 4.9.5 / Windows 11 22H2 Kerberos Incompatibility - Cross posted from r/samba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoqend/samba_495_windows_11_22h2_kerberos/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoqend/samba_495_windows_11_22h2_kerberos/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T17:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've posted this on r/samba since this is an issue with Samba, but I figured I'd cross-post it here since this is a lot larger of a community, sorry if this is something that isn't allowed. 
 I am currently running into an issue that others seem to be experiencing as well with Windows 11 22H2 and Samba 4.9.5 (issue exists with less than 4.16.2). The issue is that I cannot authenticate using Kerberos without enabling DES encryption support via GPO / Local Policy (Shown below). 
 Local Security Policy> Local Policies> Security Options> Network security: Configure encryption types allowed for Kerberos Check only DES_CBC_CRC and DES_CBC_MD5 
 When I apply this change, I am able to log into the domain and access file shares. I am not able to perform gpupdate or access Active Directory Users and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmable Switches Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xopuby/programmable_switches_use_cases/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xopuby/programmable_switches_use_cases/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T17:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone, 
 I am coming from the research community and programmable switches are big nowadays, with people pursuing research into new applications that push the boundaries of the data plane. My question is though, from the industry point of view, are programmable switches a big thing? Are they seeing more and more adoption in enterprise networks? And specifically, are there any use cases you can share?
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/anticlimacus13  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ideas for a "Thank You" Gift for non-IT types going above and beyond to help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xonlh1/ideas_for_a_thank_you_gift_for_nonit_types_going/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xonlh1/ideas_for_a_thank_you_gift_for_nonit_types_going/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T16:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All, 
 I'm looking for some clever ideas for some kind of "Thank You" gift for people inside my company who are NOT IT personnel but they go above and beyond to help out with our IT department. These people are typically in our remote offices where we have no IT support and do some of the standard "move patch cable from #x to #xx," "connect computer to internet so I can remote in," "reboot kiosk computer when frozen," etc.
 I've always thought it'd be cool to have a common gift that they can proudly display on their desk or bookshelf that shows my appreciate for them beyond the constant "Thanks YOUs" I send them via phone, email, Teams, etc. 
 Do any of you have any ideas for this type of gift? I was thinking something simple like a coffee mug or desk ornament or something along those lines. It doesn't have to be 'dirt cheap,' but I'd like to be able to afford quite a few of them and send them out then someone goes above and beyond to help out.
    submitted by    /u/Ermoore32  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sending a support request/ticket with ASAP or with high priority in Outlook will always get you pushed to the back of the queue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xon0h8/sending_a_support_requestticket_with_asap_or_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xon0h8/sending_a_support_requestticket_with_asap_or_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T15:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes. I'm that petty, fuck you.
    submitted by    /u/VjoaJR  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interface over utilisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xomp98/interface_over_utilisation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xomp98/interface_over_utilisation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T15:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 Looking for a bit of help with a problem we've had for a few weeks please.
 ​
 Background:
 ​
 MPLS network, each site has 2 routers running BGP into the WAN. Central internet breakout from an data center (EMEA or AMER). Our data centers also have MPLS routers and host a couple of server environments, a legacy environment and a production environment. 
 The problem:
 ​
 Since last August (we know the date/time with a high degree of confidence) utilisation on the external interface of one of our DC FW's has been maxed out, the switch interface it connects to is the same resulting in packet loss, slow connectivity etc. 
 The timing of the utilisation increase on these ports corresponds with one of our engineers making a mistake on the switch that connects to the inside interface of the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[DMARC] Oracle Fusion SPF pass, but we don't have a SPF record for Oracle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojut2/dmarc_oracle_fusion_spf_pass_but_we_dont_have_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojut2/dmarc_oracle_fusion_spf_pass_but_we_dont_have_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is our SPF record:
 v=spf1 include:spf.protection.outlook.com include:spf.routit.net include:spf.mandrillapp.com ~all
 Out of 110 e-mails, 93% were dmarc pass on the basis of SPF for Oracle Fusion, which is indeed sending e-mail on our behalf. Can anyone please educate me on how this is possible?
    submitted by    /u/FoamyS  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selling Used Equipment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojjeq/selling_used_equipment/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojjeq/selling_used_equipment/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good day r/sysadmin, newer I.T. manager here. 
 I have over 10 Webex Room Kits I'm looking to get rid of. We've had them for about three years, but I'd like to move our nonprofit to Teams for the license cost savings. My vendor is looking into a buyback, but that isn't moving very fast, and it's not a guaranteed solution. 
 Someone pointed out https://webuyuseditequipment.net/ but I haven't reached out there yet. Does anyone have a go-to option for getting some cash back for good equipment you don't need anymore?
    submitted by    /u/JeagerOrion  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regarding Office 365 will everyone have to set up an additional Authentication Method (MFA, SSPR), after Sept.30?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojig5/regarding_office_365_will_everyone_have_to_set_up/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojig5/regarding_office_365_will_everyone_have_to_set_up/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 Sorry if this question has been asked before but I simply can't find a clear answer anywhere.
 I work for a small firm as a developer, but since I'm the only IT'er I'm also the one who manages their office 365, even though I'm far from an expert.
 Currently I've been aware for a while now that basic authentication will be disabled and I've taken precautions so that external applications won't use this method any more.
 Just to be sure, I've enforced MFA for all the key users (but not everyone because they don't want the hassle)
 But now I'm seeing the following message in Azure:
 "Starting Sept. 30th, 2022 Combined registration experiences for MFA and SSPR will be enabled for all tenants"
 I checked and currently SSPR is disabled.
 I've been looking around and can't find a clear answer on what exactly will happen after sept. 30 for the end user.
 Will everyone have to run through the process of MFA and SSPR after oct. 1??
 In the sense that they will be logged out, and have to set up an additional authentication method?
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/Diligent-Charge-4910  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do any of you guys run Admin By Request (or similar)? If so, how is it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojaow/do_any_of_you_guys_run_admin_by_request_or/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xojaow/do_any_of_you_guys_run_admin_by_request_or/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the nature of the company, we're governed by a co-op that owns and operates the network for all of its members. Unfortunately, that means they also own AD. I'm looking for a solution that's independent of AD, but can also provide my users with local admin when needed.
    submitted by    /u/2HornsUp  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brocade hell(p)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoj79w/brocade_hellp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoj79w/brocade_hellp/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So we have been working on replacing and rebuilding a brocade stack over the weekend that the old stack bit the dust. We have the stack built, internet, ping out, ping across, but cannot ping the stack or the individual switches which is causing DNS issues. I am not onsite currently but any thoughts (other than get other switches)
    submitted by    /u/Creative_Wallaby6060  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What kind of limits do you place on Jr. Sysadmin rights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoix1d/what_kind_of_limits_do_you_place_on_jr_sysadmin/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoix1d/what_kind_of_limits_do_you_place_on_jr_sysadmin/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello,
 I'm just curious, what kind of permissions do you restrict to your Jr. Sysadmins who don't/probably shouldn't be a global administrator everywhere?
    submitted by    /u/Dizzybro  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Umbrella | DNS Filtering...or...not? (DoH)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoiulw/cisco_umbrella_dns_filteringornot_doh/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoiulw/cisco_umbrella_dns_filteringornot_doh/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 I am in the process of configuring Cisco Umbrella DNS filtering and I noticed that, whilst it wasn't working particularly well on Chrome (only blocking the first request and allowing subsequent requests straight through), it was working perfectly on Firefox.
 After doing some digging, it appears that when Chrome detects the DNS servers in use support DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH), it will automatically, unless specified by an admin policy, switch to using Secure DNS.
 With Secure DNS being served over HTTPS, this traffic no longer arrives at Umbrella on port 53 and appears to bypass DNS inspection completely.
 I have a case open with Cisco Umbrella on this one, but has anyone else come across this? Surely they haven't enabled DoH on their DNS servers and created a bypass for their own product?
 Edit: disabling Secure DNS via Group Policy for corporate users is definitely a possibility. I will have them routing via the (Secure Web Gateway) SWG so it would likely get caught there. I have intention of securing Guest WiFi users of which I have no control over their devices/browsers. This is my main concern.
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/CoyKava  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD is in TROUBLE – Ryzen 7000 Full Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_vLq2PjmIx0</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_vLq2PjmIx0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should LACP load balance the traffic on the physical links?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoihue/should_lacp_load_balance_the_traffic_on_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoihue/should_lacp_load_balance_the_traffic_on_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should the interface inside port-channel, have similar input/ouput statistics?
 ​
 ​
 there is a huge difference for interfaces in my port channel, but only for output stats, is this ok? if not, what could cause this? if someone can shed some light on it, I would appreciate it!
 ​
 interface 1
 5 minute input rate 9381000 bits/sec, 1605 packets/sec
 5 minute output rate 27875000 bits/sec, 3811 packets/sec
 524442 packets input, 382005784 bytes, 0 no buffer
 Received 18 broadcasts (18 multicasts)
 1244013 packets output, 1131945640 bytes, 0 underruns
 ​
 interface 2
 5 minute input rate 9358000 bits/sec, 1602 packets/sec
 5 minute output rate 2000 bits/sec, 2 packets/sec
 518350 packets input, 377079125 bytes, 0 no buffer
 Received 11 broadcasts (11 multicasts)
 1108 packets output, 173289 bytes, 0 underruns
    submitted by    /u/No_Tart_3957  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google SMTP - low domain reputation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoi4jg/google_smtp_low_domain_reputation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoi4jg/google_smtp_low_domain_reputation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I own a domain for exclusively personal use. My email service is properly set up with SPF/DKIM/DMARC etc (it gets 10/10 on mail-tester.com).
 However 6 weeks ago the VPS I use switched IP addresses, and suddenly Google started outright blocking my emails with the following message: 
 Our system has detected that 550-5.7.1 this message is likely suspicious due to the very low reputation of 550-5.7.1 the sending domain. To best protect our users from spam, the message 550-5.7.1 has been blocked. Please visit 550 5.7.1 https://support.google.com/mail/answer/188131 for more information. 
 I have checked all my mail logs, and there is no evidence of the domain being abused, and personally I do not send out any spam. I have since tried to fill out the Google from to have the domain unbanned twice, with no apparent results.
 My domain or IP is not listed on any blacklists, so I'm completely out of ideas...
 Google Postmaster reports both the domain and IP as having a "bad" reputation 2 days before I obtained the new IP address, so maybe the IP belonged to a spammer before?
 Does anyone know what I could try next?
    submitted by    /u/80386  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VIP wants all email and have reached Microsoft 100GB limit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoi0ov/vip_wants_all_email_and_have_reached_microsoft/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoi0ov/vip_wants_all_email_and_have_reached_microsoft/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Environemnt is O365 with the maximum 100GB being reached.
 Not wanting to remove any email as the mailbox is used for search function for every task.
 Brainstorming the best solution here. Seems moving older email to a backup external drive PST outlook file would be best and if they ever want to look at this then just have the external drive plugged in always on the laptop when opening Outlook thus still having all these emails and not reaching the 100GB limit by O365 standards?
 Curious to know what others have done in this situation when the 100GB is reached and Microsoft not really having a solution past the 100GB. *Making internal standard to just tell users such as this to remove emails and not use mailbox as search for several years in the past is not really an option as easy as that could be...
    submitted by    /u/Hxrn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notepad++ Plugins Allow Attackers to Infiltrate Systems, Achieve Persistence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xohpu2/notepad_plugins_allow_attackers_to_infiltrate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xohpu2/notepad_plugins_allow_attackers_to_infiltrate/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://www.infosecurity-magazine.com/news/notepad-plugins-attackers/
  
“In our attack scenario, the PowerShell command will execute a Meterpreter payload,” the company wrote.
 Cybereason then ran Notepad++ as ‘administrator’ and re–ran the payload, effectively managing to achieve administrative privileges on the affected system.
  
Ah, yes...
 The ol' "running-thing-as-admin-allows-you-to-run-other-thing-as-admin" vulnerability hack.
 Ingenious.
    submitted by    /u/lolklolk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Ocean Droplet for site to site VPN connection into Azure Network]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xohpdm/digital_ocean_droplet_for_site_to_site_vpn/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xohpdm/digital_ocean_droplet_for_site_to_site_vpn/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been tasked with setting up a site 2 site VPN into a clients Azure network. Out company primarily used Digital Ocean and I've spun up a droplet and installed strongswan to set up an IKEv2 connection to the client.
 We seem to keep failing at phase 2 and the returned logs from Azure say that the encryption keeps failing.
 I can't find any resources online to see if anyone else has tried this way before, am I fighting a losing battle here??
 Are Digital Oceans VM's capable of connecting to Azure via strongswan IPSec tunnels and what in the world are the encryption algorithms that match! I've tried several and can't find any that suit both sides.
    submitted by    /u/Dafft_Ladd  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The processing of group policy failed internal system error]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xohmhu/the_processing_of_group_policy_failed_internal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xohmhu/the_processing_of_group_policy_failed_internal/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:15:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good afternoon 
 Just looking for some advice,
 I’ve noriced a lot of my servers are reporting group policy errors under the system log stating ‘The processing of group policy failed internal system error’ and to check the operational log. I’ve checked this log and can’t see any errors? 
 I’ve filtered the event ID 1125 on one particular server and it’s very random. One day it happened 4 times, another day twice and some days not at all. I’m really stumped, nothing appears broken on the GPO front, the furthest the error ID 1125 goes back is Jan 2022. Looking back through them again it’s very random when the error is logged. 
 Just curious if anyone else has these event IDs regularly in their environment 
 Thank you
    submitted by    /u/Clear_Kale5947  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blocking DNS resolution by country?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xohhqz/blocking_dns_resolution_by_country/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xohhqz/blocking_dns_resolution_by_country/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T12:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all, I'll start off by saying I'm not sure this is possible given my limited understanding of DNS, but... Is it possible to block DNS requests to resolving to a specific country's IP range?
 Currently we are blocking all outbound traffic to a country on the FW but occasionally a DNS request for a service will resolve to server there. We'd like only responses to be from other servers in the region even tho country X might be closest.
 Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/C3PU  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HP ProCurve ACL assistance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xogegg/hp_procurve_acl_assistance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xogegg/hp_procurve_acl_assistance/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T11:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am trying to figure out what I am missing. I have created an access list on a procurve 5400 and assigned it to a VLAN using ip access-group "BYOD" in. When the ACL is set, I cannot access the internet, but can resolve names, I have not got a proxy set. Am I missing something? Am I right in thinking that after 30 permit there is essentially a 'block everything' not already defined style rule?
 ip access-list extended "BYOD" 10 permit udp 0.0.0.0 255.255.255.255 10.1.1.10 0.0.0.0 eq 67 20 permit udp 0.0.0.0 255.255.255.255 10.1.1.10 0.0.0.0 eq 68 30 permit udp 0.0.0.0 255.255.255.255 10.1.1.10 0.0.0.0 eq 53 exit 
 From the examples I have seen online, I don't have to add the gateway address or anything? Or should I be naming specific address ranges that the client shouldn't be able to access and then setting a permit ip any any underneath 30 permit udp....
 Thanks for any guidance you can give.
    submitted by    /u/mattmickeyj  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do i centrally manage certificates in HTTP/2 like ssl-termination?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xofqt4/how_do_i_centrally_manage_certificates_in_http2/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xofqt4/how_do_i_centrally_manage_certificates_in_http2/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T10:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ssl-termination operates only as a FULL-PROXY and has the advantage of unified certificate management. 
 When HTTP/2 is used, even if the backend (server-side) is h2c, it is impossible to centralize the certificate.
 Does HTTP/2 discard the advantage of certificate workday management? Should I just manage the certificate with CI/CD?
    submitted by    /u/chop-stick-7502  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[RANT] I hate product based certifications for boring software e.g antimalware crap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xofnkh/rant_i_hate_product_based_certifications_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xofnkh/rant_i_hate_product_based_certifications_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T10:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So in the past few years I have been constantly dealing with super bad quality video courses of software companies in order to get their "tEcHnIcAl CeRtiFiCaTion".
 Most of them were some sort of backup service, antimalware crap, pentesting stuff like acunetix, you get the idea.
 The other day for example, I had to do a certificate for an anti malware client like kasperski or norton and the company left in multiple retakes of lines he had to do.
 He either had to cough or didn't get the pronunciation right and went: "aw damn, gotta do the line again - OK! - bla bla" and went on with the rest of the script.
 I just don't get why you would make them so unprofessionally.
 Now I do get that people can be overworked and struggle to get the video out in time, because this might not even be their actual job.
 The company probably had to get the video out in time, but come on man, this is just such a pain to watch and retrieve information from.
 Also what's up with non native english speakers putting out english tutorials in shitty english?
 We're talking about companies that make literally dozens of millions of buckeroos per year in profit.
 It's just so damn of putting. 
 Some sentences sound like questions, but are not questions
 Some sentences are grammatically incorrect
 Some sentences are being mumbled
 Some words are used in the wrong way 
 And don't get me started on flashy graphics in the video that don't have to do anything with the product itself and the cheesy, soft gitarre music in the background.
 Do you get what I mean? 
 I'm probably just fed up with having to do these wannabe technical certifications, so that our company get's better pricing for said product, but damn... 
 I think I need to look for another job.
    submitted by    /u/Own_Blueberry7724  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure type 5 eVPN routes with FRR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xof233/pure_type_5_evpn_routes_with_frr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xof233/pure_type_5_evpn_routes_with_frr/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T10:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying to make FRR (Linux) to use pure type 5 routes in eVPN. I was able to make it work with L2 (vxlans in a bridges), but I'm interested in a pure L3, and I have trouble to find any guides or docs.
 Can someone give me a direction or snippet from config for FRR?
    submitted by    /u/amarao_san  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moronic Monday - September 26, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoexsh/moronic_monday_september_26_2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoexsh/moronic_monday_september_26_2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T10:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howdy, /r/sysadmin!
 It's that time of the week, Moronic Monday! This is a safe (mostly) judgement-free environment for all of your questions and stories, no matter how silly you think they are. Anybody can answer questions! My name is AutoModerator and I've taken over responsibility for posting these weekly threads so you don't have to worry about anything except your comments!
    submitted by    /u/AutoModerator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you update Always on VPN Device tunnel config?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoegz8/how_do_you_update_always_on_vpn_device_tunnel/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoegz8/how_do_you_update_always_on_vpn_device_tunnel/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T09:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short version:
 According to docs, this config is stored in WMI as XML
 How to update it when you need to add some changes - new routes or additional aovpn server or something else stored in that $ProfileXML?
 Longer version:
 On first thought easy solution to update XML would be to just remove old CIM instance and then create new but there's downside - if there's any reason new one won't be created (some mistake in config or any other reason) - the connection to this remote device might be lost and we'll need to intervene with manual connection to affected workstation or laptop and do the manual troubleshooting, running scripts etc.
 So that's why I'm looking for a way to update config instead.
 My current logic is that every time laptop wakes up from sleep (gets out of idle or lid is ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What News/Podcasts/Videos do you Start Your Day With?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoeb6v/what_newspodcastsvideos_do_you_start_your_day_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoeb6v/what_newspodcastsvideos_do_you_start_your_day_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T09:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m realising that most of my news and media consumption isn’t exactly tailored to the world I enjoy living in. So I’m looking to change that with my morning ritual.
 So! All that being said, are there any Daily / Weekly Podcasts, Videos, Newsfeeds you folks Consume Regularly? Specifically I’m a Microsoft guy, so I’m looking for PowerPlatform items, Azure Items, and 365 Items.
    submitted by    /u/Psyclown02  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Help getting into this profession (UK)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodynd/help_getting_into_this_profession_uk/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodynd/help_getting_into_this_profession_uk/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T09:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have always been good with computers as ive spent a good amount of my life on them, i even tought myself how to code at a basic level. I am 32 now in a dead end job and its always been in my mind that when i have had enough of my job i can get into IT. I have been in the same job for 10 years now earning minimum wage, struggling every month to get by and i cant even tell you why i have done that, i have hated every single day but ive just stuck with it because its the easy option i suppose. 
 To top it off my girlfriend is now pregnant and its hit me, I really need to step up now and get my arse in gear.
 I would love advice on what is the best area to get into, and what i need to learn. I am UK based in Manchester so i would want to obviously work in this area. I truly believe i could pick up anything pretty quickly, I am hungry guys, something has clicked in my head finally.
    submitted by    /u/EraHCS  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternative to RDS gateway?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodwq8/alternative_to_rds_gateway/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodwq8/alternative_to_rds_gateway/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T09:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m planning on setting up a small development environment at work on a server behind a vpn with no access to the internet. I’ve previously used the built in gateway without a license (becuase lazy) and that has come to haunt me later so im looking to see if there is any alternative for this? 
 The problem is just that i cant use up many IP’s on the range and need a single entry point to a separate lab lan of sorts. 
 Thoughts that have crossed my mind is using Traefik or pfsense and port forwarding but im not sure this is the easier way of doing things. Any suggestions on how to solve it?
    submitted by    /u/thatfhc  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RDS Windows Start Menu Disabled?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodq98/rds_windows_start_menu_disabled/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodq98/rds_windows_start_menu_disabled/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T08:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Guys,
 Quick question: do you guys know what GPO disables Windows button / start menu?
 The old Sysadmin disabled this but I want to renable this.
 I'm checking the RDS Lockdown Policies OU but I can't seem to find it. 
 Does anybody know which policy would cause this? 
 Thanks for the help & kind regards!
    submitted by    /u/Ghostky123  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Server patching and Post Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodk66/windows_server_patching_and_post_verification/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xodk66/windows_server_patching_and_post_verification/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T08:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all,
 We use SCCM. However, SCCM can not perform the post-verification test and send a report. 
 We have 400+ servers and we are verifying manually. So how do we automate this and create a report?
 Ex: AD Server / DHCP /DNS / SQL / APP /IIS /etc etc
    submitted by    /u/EducationAlert5209  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visible calendars for organization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xode61/visible_calendars_for_organization/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xode61/visible_calendars_for_organization/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T08:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
 anyone knows if there are any way to manage the visibility for every users calendar? For example we want to be able to see everyones appointments in their calendar and also see the title of the booking - not just the appointment with a 'busy'-title.
    submitted by    /u/synxz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bypass RD Gateway sever from local addresses not working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xod8tx/bypass_rd_gateway_sever_from_local_addresses_not/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xod8tx/bypass_rd_gateway_sever_from_local_addresses_not/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T08:22:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I have an issue where some of my clients (thin clients) connects through the gateway server instead of direct connects. I have enabled the settings Bypass RD Gateway server for local addresses. 
 This problem occurs when connecting from the RDWeb site.
 If I do a direct connection from the RD Client it is working. 
 All my clients are on remote networks connected by VPN so the RDS severs and the clients are on different subnets. 
 DNS lookups is OK, for example I can ping all addresses both by server name and fqdn.
 Also tested to open all ports in the vpn tunnel but the same problem occurs. 
 The strange thing is that not all clients or remote offices have this problem and they are setup identically so I can’t find what is causing this. 
 Any ideas? 
 Connection broker/RDWEB/RDGatway Windows 2016
 RDSH Windows 2019
    submitted by    /u/Oskar_2000  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When adding Exchange and AD to symantec protection, what are some settings that need to be set up for these 2?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xod17t/when_adding_exchange_and_ad_to_symantec/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xod17t/when_adding_exchange_and_ad_to_symantec/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T08:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusions and etc. or does symantec by default do everything
    submitted by    /u/hwehwegwhgewe23  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S3 bucket SSL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xocc9h/s3_bucket_ssl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xocc9h/s3_bucket_ssl/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T07:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do I prevent non-SSL traffic in an AWS S3 bucket?
 Where do we set this up?
    submitted by    /u/anacondaonline  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASA vpn helpful commands to investigate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoc1vj/asa_vpn_helpful_commands_to_investigate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xoc1vj/asa_vpn_helpful_commands_to_investigate/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T07:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello
 I was tasked to migrate 10 legacy asa clusters (versions 7.x-8.x, ASA-50XX) to other vendor while never worked with cisco. No ASDM available.
 As I am understanding it slowly in general, vpns were always something I had least exposure to. Could anyone suggest how to effectively confirm if VPNs are still used on those?
 Currently Im evaluating if vpns are to be migrated or no. Some have vpn configs, others don't..So on those where I see it:
 As I understand, seeing live tunnel is best direct evidence of it being used (show vpn-sessiondb)
 In case I do not see it at time of it being established - are there some stats in cli available that would tell me if it was used say last month and how many times? If no stats tied to dates, anything that could help is appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/Flash4473  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac Table Size Ethernet Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xobe3e/mac_table_size_ethernet_switch/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xobe3e/mac_table_size_ethernet_switch/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T06:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am working on Ethernet switch on FPGA. I have 8192 MAC addresses, I am trying to create the MAC table by passing them through the 16-bit Hash algorithm. I have a few questions about this;
 I use the hash algorithm result as the address port of the block RAM which I use as the mac table. In this way, I complete the search process in 1 clock cycle, but for the 16-bit HASH algorithm, a very large RAM of 2^16 = 65536 addresses is created. Only 8192 addresses of 65536 addresses are used, the rest remains empty. I don't know how to do this more efficiently. Thank you in advance for your help.
    submitted by    /u/Melik_Sen  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing Microsoft Visio LTSC Standard 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xob3ut/installing_microsoft_visio_ltsc_standard_2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xob3ut/installing_microsoft_visio_ltsc_standard_2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T06:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Purchased a copy of Visio LTSC Standard 2021through Journey Ed for a user. Downloaded it from the Microsoft Volume Licensing center. Every time I try running the installer, it fails after a few seconds, giving a "Couldn't Install" error with error code 0-2054 (0). I have tried uninstalling all other versions of Office from the device, disabled firewall, and after hours of additional troubleshooting, finally resorted to completely wiping the computer and re-installing Windows 10. Even after this, with literally nothing on the computer but a stock Windows 10 install, I get this error. I decided to try installing this on a completely different computer just to test, and sure enough, that one gets the same error. Any idea how I can install the volume license version of Visio successfully?
    submitted by    /u/fabio_santino  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AD Password Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xob2dz/new_ad_password_policy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xob2dz/new_ad_password_policy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T06:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to set a new password policy in AD for normal users.
 Currently it is:
  
8 characters
 Expires after half a year
 Complexity required
  
​
 My draft for a new policy:
  
14 characters
 Password does not expire
 No complexity
 Also regular matching with hashes of haveibeenpwned
  
What is my goal? Users should set a secure passphrase once instead of insecure iterations of the same password over and over (password!01, password!02, and so on). The password should only be changed in case of a suspected breach.
 What do you think? I am actually quite convinced not to let passwords expire at all. But in many publications you can still read that they should rotate every 42 days. :|
    submitted by    /u/catredcat  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintenance windows for windows server scheduled tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoag6r/maintenance_windows_for_windows_server_scheduled/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xoag6r/maintenance_windows_for_windows_server_scheduled/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T05:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have a Windows server running a number of scheduled tasks mostly to move files around, upload/download to SFTP, etc...
 Wondering if is is possible to create maintenance windows to prevent schedule tasks launching during scheduled downtime of dependent services i.e. network shares?
 Otherwise I just need to remember to shut the server down, then turn on when scheduled downtime ends.
    submitted by    /u/scottmoremates  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What branch of IT makes profit instead of being an expense?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo9ygi/what_branch_of_it_makes_profit_instead_of_being/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo9ygi/what_branch_of_it_makes_profit_instead_of_being/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T05:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone said this on a previous threat and I'm curious about your answers.
 ​
 EDIT: I've been in IT for 3 years close to 4, and I'm trying to decide if I should just become an expert in an IT Field or switch over to a more profitable path (SE, Data Analytics, Etc.).
    submitted by    /u/supreme_jackk  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who has experienced a lazy/unmotivated coworker?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo9fnd/who_has_experienced_a_lazyunmotivated_coworker/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo9fnd/who_has_experienced_a_lazyunmotivated_coworker/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T04:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And how did you avoid getting blamed for any issues because the lazy colleague doesn't do anything?
 My current issue is, that I am supposed to transition support for an application to a colleague. The colleague has been involved with app support for the past two years. He has made zero contributions to any scripts, processes or improvements. A few months ago I figured out he hasn't logged into the app in several months. Now that I am transitioning support to him, he only does support when specifically asked. No insightful questions, or how does XYZ work, or request for meetings to show feature ABC. I am the one who has to chase him to show him how to do things.
 During a critical issue where I was on the call with the vendor, the colleague seemed "Away" in Teams. I told my manager (tactfully) that I need to show my colleague how the issue was resolved, but he is away. Manager just said, "Yes, continue to work with him and let him do the work".
 I have a feeling this will come back to me some how. I was thinking of keeping a record of all meetings, how-to sessions, meeting invites etc. Later on, if this does come back to me, I will just my manager what was done to transition support.
    submitted by    /u/txs2300  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frustrating network issue with small business client]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo5ktx/frustrating_network_issue_with_small_business/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo5ktx/frustrating_network_issue_with_small_business/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T01:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work with a small business that has ATT fiber and a hosted VoIP phone system. For the last 2 weeks they have experienced issues with their desk phones dropping calls and losing the ability to dial out intermittently throughout the day. No changes were made on this network before these occurrences. 
 We first called the phone vendor and asked them to troubleshoot, they told us that the phones run over the internet so as long as we can confirm internet is stable then the phones should work. They also recommended we call ATT and have them disable their SIP-ALG settings for our circuit. 
 Called ATT and had them disable SIP-ALG, but the problems continued. 
 I should also note that I have sat a full day at this clients office and monitored multiple ping tests to different internal and external devices and never noticed any drops, even when the phones would disconnect.
 This network has only a WatchGuard firewall and a netgear PoE switch in front of the phones, I've replaced both of these devices in hopes that one of them were faulty. Issue still persisted and phones continue to drop.
 Client is pissed, vendors pointing fingers, any suggestions appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/hzh24  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Surface abuse on the NFL 😭😭 #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ee08Ko9E_XU</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ee08Ko9E_XU"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T01:20:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Windows Central</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Education recommendation.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo4jal/education_recommendation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo4jal/education_recommendation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Everyone! Using a Throwaway!
 Thanks for reading! I've been lurking and laughing along with you all for a few months now. I'm hoping you can give me some advice.
 In the past few years I transitioned from a chef, to an operations manager and sys admin of a commodity trading group. They had some unsecure and inefficient practices, like all users logging into a single email account. I'm sure you can all imagine some of the other things they came up with.
 Once hired I purchased a domain, and implemented messaging software. This business receives an enormous amount of email and I really enjoyed creating systems that helped them be more aware of what was happening.
 I don't anticipate leaving but I am planning on taking courses to help me stay in the field when I need to leave this company.
 Can anyone recommend meaningful courses I can take outside of a degree that could help further my career as a sys admin?
 ​
 Thank you!!!
    submitted by    /u/QuiGonnJimm  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do I need another router or can I use a managed switch?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo46fa/do_i_need_another_router_or_can_i_use_a_managed/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo46fa/do_i_need_another_router_or_can_i_use_a_managed/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'll preface this by saying I'm fairly new to the networking world so I apologize if this is a stupid question. I've been asked to set up a network at this medium-sized church and I'm not quite sure what the best option is. The ISP installed a fiber connection to replace the preexisting DSL. They installed a Cisco 4300 series router and gave us a static IP to use. Because the router belongs to them I can't configure it in any way. It doesn't have DHCP set up so I have to manually set everything up. The church already had a cisco SG350-28P 28-Port Gigabit PoE Managed Switch that they had connected directly to the Cisco router.
 ​
  
I need to know if it is possible to use the managed switch for routing or if will i need to install another router. 
 If I were to use the switch for routing what would that look like and would it pose security risks?
  
   submitted by    /u/-theflop-  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Question to ESXI admins? Switching?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo41wv/question_to_esxi_admins_switching/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo41wv/question_to_esxi_admins_switching/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm seeing the occasional odd post of Admin's with escalated projects to rip out ESXI of their environment.
 I was just wondering if this is happening industry wide?
 And if you are, may I ask what you are migrating too?
    submitted by    /u/TestUser12358  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do sysadmins - on average - earn way less than do devs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo3q4d/why_do_sysadmins_on_average_earn_way_less_than_do/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo3q4d/why_do_sysadmins_on_average_earn_way_less_than_do/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wouldn't it make sense to pay the guys maintaining your entire infra really fucking good?
    submitted by    /u/CrazyJoe83xx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moronic Monday!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo37ya/moronic_monday/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo37ya/moronic_monday/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Monday, you've not yet had coffee and the week ahead is gonna suck. Let's open the floor for a weekly Stupid Questions Thread, so we can all ask those questions we're too embarrassed to ask!
 Post your question - stupid or otherwise - here to get an answer. Anyone can post a question and the community as a whole is invited and encouraged to provide an answer. Serious answers are not expected.
 Note: This post is created at 01:00 UTC. It may not be Monday where you are in the world, no need to comment on it.
    submitted by    /u/AutoModerator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Internet Routes...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo2i67/full_internet_routes/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xo2i67/full_internet_routes/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T23:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building two new data centers and current have four ISP's planned for each of them. Each ISP is 1G for now and could be upgrading to 10G down the road.. Today our old DC's running dual ISP and using ASR1001-X with mem upgraded to 16G with full inet routes. So for each ISP we had an ASR and then peer the two ASR's. From there we had 3850X (Stack) setup as core with EIGRP taking the default route only. Idea was just get the traffic to one of the ASR's and BGP best path would kick in. Again for the most part it worked pretty well.
 But with us stepping it up to four ISP's the old design is just not going to work, we've seem to be maxing out the ASR1001-X with two full tables (which is maxed out at 16G) so this isn't going to work.
 So looking for a Edge router that can handle two to four full inet tables. For the core thinking we can just do what we did before as these 3850X should have zero issues with 4G maxed across all four ISP's or even 40G if all upgraded to 10G each.
 Or is there something else out we should be looking at for the core switches as well?
 ​
 Thanks in advance...
    submitted by    /u/galluccib  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoping for insight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo1rfy/hoping_for_insight/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo1rfy/hoping_for_insight/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T22:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, what's up,,,,, I saw your thread and was wondering if anyone had any insight about getting in to an entry level position for IT. I am currently a little over have way done with my AAS in cyber-sec. Needless to say I am getting VERY nervous for what comes after I graduate.
 Any help you can provide will be greatly appreciated.
 thank you for taking the time to read and respond......Also I am in the US, Colorado.
    submitted by    /u/_guy_over_there_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who owns your Code and Scripts?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo1khe/who_owns_your_code_and_scripts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xo1khe/who_owns_your_code_and_scripts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T22:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having not applied for a SysAdmin in the past, I'm not sure how to approach this. 
 Is the there a standard for scripts and code you create? Is is assumed to be the property of your employer?
 I'm thinking in terms of some unique way in which I might use a block of code, or an entire script or program.
 What's the best way to look at this?
    submitted by    /u/RandomXUsr  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hmm make it Mountain Dew and you might get me.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnzsyt/hmm_make_it_mountain_dew_and_you_might_get_me/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnzsyt/hmm_make_it_mountain_dew_and_you_might_get_me/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T21:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just came across this in my junk folder. Interesting way to buy my attention. What's some one cold calls that have drawn you in?
 ​
 One IT person to another...could also send you a sick throwback Star Wars shirt if that sounds more fun. 
 Just trying to honestly earn 5 minutes to discuss securing your cloud backups. No fluff. Thanks for letting me be persistent. 
  
From: Charles
 Date: Tue Sep 20 09:14:23 CEST 2022
 To: "Ryan
 Subject: 4 cases? 
 Throw in a 4th? 
 From: Charles
 Date: Fri Sep 16 15:07:44 CEST 2022
 To: "Ryan
 Subject: one month of Dr. Pepper
 Ryan, 
 Few things beat Dr. Pepper. Especially when dealing with late-night system upgrades. 
 Trade you one month's supply (3 cases?) for 11 minutes to show you a strategy for making sure your cloud backups are secure? 
 Thanks,Chuck
 Chuck 
  
Edit: Removed link pasted email
    submitted by    /u/RyanLewis2010  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Route tage or community strings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xnzojf/route_tage_or_community_strings/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xnzojf/route_tage_or_community_strings/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T21:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wanted to post a question without getting into the entire topology of my network environment to get people's opinions and experiences of what you all have done. We have a network change/design opportunity and I am wanting to eliminate some route redistribution between OSPF and BGP. We use BGP for WAN routers to some of our sites around the state. We have remote connectivity from all around our state via our private fiber network, DMVPN tunnels (iWAN), and various peerings with Telco providers. We do this via 2 different data centers where we peer with different Telco routers via BGP, Cisco's iWAN, and our statewide aggregation routers that connect to our private fiber network across the state. The fiber network continues to grow as we lay more and more down each year. We bring those BGP routes into OSPF via route maps that have prefix lists attached to them. I wanted to go more into BGP and stop the route redistribution wherever I can. 
 I am wondering if I should use BGP community values or route tags to allow our sites all around the state to determine what the best path to take would be. Basically every one of our remote locations have several methods of communication back to the data centers. I would like to make one path look better, and fail over, or be able to easily switch paths by changing a route map somewhere centrally to our data center. So if I change a value of a community string or route tag, all the sites switch paths at the same time, should I decide that needs to happen. Am I going down the right path here? Are route tags the best way to do this, or are community values the standard way to do this?
    submitted by    /u/bardsleyb  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving Myself Bonkers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnzlim/driving_myself_bonkers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnzlim/driving_myself_bonkers/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T21:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the panic hit my company had to downsize. During that time I accepted a lot of tasks. After we got over the hump and started growing I was promoted to management and willed myself to hold on to my task, do automation, keep up with new technology, become the one stop shop for Azure. It all came to a head last week and I walked out for a long weekend breather. Quieting my mind I think I have determined I simply cannot be everyone, be an individual contributor, and manage. I have to pick. I think I am going to continue to be a manager, grow my team, and be the muscle that moves the company's technology forward.
 I still have the desire to learn Linux, establish powershell 7, get into Ansible, make the assets management system and much more but I guess those days are going to have to be behind me.
 Has this realization come to any of you?
    submitted by    /u/whatnownova  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the learning curve for server “level” hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnz3o8/on_the_learning_curve_for_server_level_hardware/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnz3o8/on_the_learning_curve_for_server_level_hardware/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T21:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys, So basically I am a developer (front end web and backend) but for years I always messed around with web hosting. Setting up servers, etc. I’ve always been SUPER into hardware (passion).
 But lately I’ve been setting up our new hosting servers for the company im at because they trusted me enough to move from managed hosting environment to rented servers where we manage the hosting ourselves.
 Most hosting clients are past clients where we made their sites. We host a few hundred but obviously want to increase.
 Im looking into collocation, but honestly I’m super surprised at the cost of servers. We are in South Africa so there aren’t many big DC providers. So only when we get a few servers would we look at collocation, but how “worth it” is hardware like Xeon CPU’s? I see there are now some new Intel consumer level CPUs that support ECC, and most new AMD CPUs support ECC. So for largely Wordpress and NodeJS environments is there an issue with going with AMD? Is there something I’m missing?
 Honestly I’m just not sure where to start with hardware, I’ve learnt what I can in theory, but real world reasons for certain choices, and advice is very different. 
 This post was a bit of a ramble but I guess I’m just looking for any good nuggets from you pros 🙂
    submitted by    /u/Jordz2203  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reset Bios PW of HP Envy x360]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnz1ck/reset_bios_pw_of_hp_envy_x360/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnz1ck/reset_bios_pw_of_hp_envy_x360/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T21:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I might've messed up. I own an HP Envy x360 convertible for private use and apparently set an administrator password for it some day and well, being me, didn't document it.
 Whilst I remember the power on password and can therefore still use this thing, the UEFI is out of reach for me.
 Is there any way, at all, to reset the password on a notebook like this, or am I forced to send it in? I'm no stranger to disassembling laptops, but would like to refrain from anything voiding the warranty (so soldering out EPROMs is out of question, unfortunately).
    submitted by    /u/ThisIsTenou  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guide: How to Authenticate to the Microsoft Graph API using PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnyvtt/guide_how_to_authenticate_to_the_microsoft_graph/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnyvtt/guide_how_to_authenticate_to_the_microsoft_graph/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T20:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've gotten a number of questions and folks interested in the Graph API, but struggle a bit regarding authentication. Often times once you get past this hurdle the rest is relatively easy. 
 Decided to put a guide together in case it saves anyone a headache:
 https://www.nkasco.com/blog/2022/9/25/how-to-authenticate-to-the-microsoft-graph-api-using-powershell
    submitted by    /u/nkasco  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone still have any HPE ProCurve 2848s running ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnyn1h/anyone_still_have_any_hpe_procurve_2848s_running/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnyn1h/anyone_still_have_any_hpe_procurve_2848s_running/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T20:48:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or am I the only one that still sees 20 year old switches ?
    submitted by    /u/CyberHouseChicago  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 - Active Directory + Gold Image or Intune + Hybrid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnx3no/windows_11_active_directory_gold_image_or_intune/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnx3no/windows_11_active_directory_gold_image_or_intune/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T19:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/jasonin951  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how do we make use of 16 million VNIs when we only have 4000 vlans?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xnw2bd/how_do_we_make_use_of_16_million_vnis_when_we/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xnw2bd/how_do_we_make_use_of_16_million_vnis_when_we/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T19:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IE, I've got a basic VxLAN network up, only mapping 2-3 VLANs to VNIs, but what's the point of having 16 million VNIs if theres only 4000 vlans to link them too?
    submitted by    /u/FuckBruceArians  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever actually been to your company's DC? Is it lights out?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnvj3r/have_you_ever_actually_been_to_your_companys_dc/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnvj3r/have_you_ever_actually_been_to_your_companys_dc/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T18:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have on-prem and a DC.
 In the last two companies, I've worked at I was never in DC. Then talking to a coworker at my new job this company has a lights-out policy where no one is allowed inside the DC except for emergencies or the planned maintenance window on the first weekend of the month. There are security guards at the gate but that is all. Even the operators work remotely. Exciting stuff!
    submitted by    /u/bustedbutthole  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is CISCO ISE always going to be the big dog? Or is there another similar product going to take over? Or has it already happened?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnts3u/is_cisco_ise_always_going_to_be_the_big_dog_or_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnts3u/is_cisco_ise_always_going_to_be_the_big_dog_or_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T17:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m wanting to maybe point my wheel toward a specific area, cisco ISE. I’d like to get CCNP SEC-ISE.
 But I just wanna make sure something bigger isn’t gonna take over or already has.
    submitted by    /u/BobbyDoWhat  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated SSL cert on server not being used by all clients...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnt6jh/updated_ssl_cert_on_server_not_being_used_by_all/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnt6jh/updated_ssl_cert_on_server_not_being_used_by_all/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We updated a SSL certificate on our web server yesterday, and most clients are seeing the new cert but there is a subset that is still using the old cert (which is expiring this week). Is there some kind of function in Windows that saves a certificate for a website locally, and uses it by default for a period of time? Is there a timeout that forces Windows to recheck/revalidate the cert on a particular website? and is there a way to force a client to ignore any cached certs and check the cert on the server instead? and what might happen if the client uses a cached cert?
    submitted by    /u/jwckauman  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What cyberscurty attack tools could I demonstrate for a school project?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnswby/what_cyberscurty_attack_tools_could_i_demonstrate/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnswby/what_cyberscurty_attack_tools_could_i_demonstrate/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T17:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently taking a cybersecurity course and one of the major projects that we will be starting soon is a demonstration on either a) an attack on a private network or b) a successful mitigation of an attack. What kind of cool scripts / programs / tools should I look into to demonstrate? I personally want to do a mix of both, where I demonstrate an attack, and then show the steps I would take to mitigate it.
    submitted by    /u/Silverwoods2  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I LOVE Paywalls. Thanks Intel!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4V_pYA7Uq0U</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4V_pYA7Uq0U"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T16:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VLAN a New SSID with Server doing DHCP, Sophos UTM 9 firewall and 3 Cisco Switches and Unifi Access Points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xns4u6/vlan_a_new_ssid_with_server_doing_dhcp_sophos_utm/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xns4u6/vlan_a_new_ssid_with_server_doing_dhcp_sophos_utm/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T16:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a network that has Server 2016 running DHCP, Sophos UTM 9 firewall, 3 Cisco CBS250 switches and Unifi access points. They are running out of IP addresses at this location, and I was wanting to create a new SSID and put it on a different IP range so that users can connect devices to that network and work with their mobile devices and laptops.
 I have setup a VLAN for that the SSID in Unifi and created a new Scope in the DHCP server. I also set the firewall DHCP relay to point to the DHCP server so anything looking for those requests can find that IP range. 
 I have setup something like this a few times in other devices using Unifi but in this current setup I am unfamiliar with Cisco and Sophos. I have figured a lot out by Googling and watching videos but I can’t seem to find this exact scenario that I am trying to recreate. 
 I am wondering if I can just setup the DHCP scope, set the network inside of Unifi with the new IP range and point the DHCP relay to the firewall without using VLAN or if I need to use VLAN how I can get it to function properly across the network.
 Do I have to create a VLAN in the Sophos for this or do I just need to tag the firewall and point the DHCP relay back to the server? Also the switches are Layer 3 which I honestly have never used personally. I have been reading up about them but still unclear how I can utilize the layer 3 in this situation. 
 I hope my post doesn’t get locked this time for being low quality. I hardly ever ask anyone for help when trying to do stuff and figure it out on my own but this one has me over thinking everything.
    submitted by    /u/Revolver034  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell hard drive in HP server?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnr54x/dell_hard_drive_in_hp_server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnr54x/dell_hard_drive_in_hp_server/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T15:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm running an HP DL380 G6 (2.5'') and I just bought this hard disk: G8FVT Compellent 1TB 7.2k SAS 2.5" 12G Hard Drive, the hard drive seems to be a Dell G8FVT, compatible with SCv2000, SCv3000 and SC4000 series.
 My concern is that I can't find this drive listed anywhere on this website, is this going to be an issue or is the drive going to work just fine?
 Just want to clarify, I'm not using any HP drives on my system currently, just random ones I found, though those were listed on that website. This is for a home lab, nothing too serious or mission critical.
    submitted by    /u/MrMyCheese  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you actually buy "enterprise-grade" SSDs or HDDs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnqugm/do_you_actually_buy_enterprisegrade_ssds_or_hdds/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnqugm/do_you_actually_buy_enterprisegrade_ssds_or_hdds/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T15:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm having this conversation now with a smaller shop. They want to set up a new NAS with RAID syncing to a second NAS at a remote site. They already had a setup like this running with WD Blue HDDs but it's almost 10 years old and ready to update. The admin there read he needs "enterprise drives" and I'm like no you don't. They are more than three times the cost of the SSDs in the drive and for this setup way overkill. 
 15-20 years ago when hard drives weren't nearly as reliable I'd more inclined to agree but now not so much. Especially when the place I work at has well over a million SSDs and HDDs in their DCs around the world and all of them are your standard off-the-shelf Western Digitals or Seagates and it's running fine.
    submitted by    /u/bustedbutthole  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firewall confusion...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xnqo0n/firewall_confusion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xnqo0n/firewall_confusion/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T15:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am designing a hypothetical network for a homework assignment. It is fairly simple thus far, but this question I have is proving more difficult to answer than I expected. I have watched networking educational videos, I've looked for sources, but it seems that my firewall implementation idea is somehow novel, though I am certain it is not. Or, perhaps it is such a dumb idea that it does not exist online. 
 I want to segment my network. Simple enough. My idea was to use firewalls at the edge of each network segment ("star" topology central router leads to firewalls at each outgoing port for the various departments) for high security. 
 Is this... Reasonable? I only seem to find network segmenting that simply uses switches, but with no firewall other than that which leads to the WAN or DMZ. Additionally, how would these firewalls generally be configured? I would imagine I could allow only the ports that are reasonable for that segment's network usage?
 Also, can I use application proxy gateways at the edge of network segments? Online sources imply that proxies should only be used at the outside edge of the LAN. I want one proxy for one department, but a different proxy for another. Each then accessing the central router of the star topology. 
 TL;DR can firewalls be reasonably used as a security measure for multiple internal network segments? What might that look like for security purposes? Same question for application proxy gateways?
    submitted by    /u/CreedyBabyBoi  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice needed | Cable vs Microwave for building internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xno11r/advice_needed_cable_vs_microwave_for_building/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xno11r/advice_needed_cable_vs_microwave_for_building/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T13:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, we have two buildings, eight units in each building, and we are looking at doing a bulk internet deal for them.
 We are deciding between a line of sight (microwave?) Service with asynchronous up/down speeds vs dedicated modems to each unit via cable provider.
 Both offers are priced similarly and have 5 year contract terms. (4-5% yearly increase in price) The microwave provider is everywhere wireless. They would deploy redundant equipment, backup power supplies, and service equipment. We own it after 7 years. Speeds are 500Mbps or 1 Gbps, but not higher at the moment.
 My question.. I'm not sure how to evaluate the microwave offering and if it will be superior to the cable modem in each unit. Latency/jitter, etc. What should we consider? I can ask one of their other recent deployments to test their system.
 From a risk perspective, the DOCSIS4 rollout will possibly drive down prices of cable offerings (at least introductory prices), and we'll be paying more in three years than we negotiate today.
    submitted by    /u/techDad_312  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[External USB HD with sleep mode and persistent ISCSI targetcli connection.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnnryz/external_usb_hd_with_sleep_mode_and_persistent/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnnryz/external_usb_hd_with_sleep_mode_and_persistent/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T13:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I have a external 4TB USB Disc that goes to sleep when it is not accessed for a certain time.
 It this model in 4TB: https://www.tradeinn.com/techinn/en/intenso-memory-center-3.5-usb-3.0-6tb-external-hdd-hard-drive/137796299/p
 I access this disc via ISCSI on a Debian system. I noticed that this disc becomes unavailable as ISCSI Target, once it has gone to sleep because apparently the drive name changes and it gets a new device name usually the next free letter for example instead of /dev/sdd it changes to /dev/sdf messing up my targetcli setup.
 I followed advice and instead of the device name I pointed targetcli to /dev/disk/by-id/...
 But unforutnately that did not help either. After sleeping the disc will not be accessible on ISCSI.
 I'd prefer to have the Disc continue to go to sleep in order to save energy, but still want it to wake up and be available on iscsi. On windows, I also sometimes had issues with the disc not being detected anymore once it went to sleep. It usually helped to rescan for the USB devices to redetect the disc. Also manually reswitching the power button helped.
 Is there any way to make sure that targetcli keeps the external hd connected, even if it goes to sleep on Linux Debian/Ubuntu?
    submitted by    /u/Spam00r  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dell Mobile Workstation Purchasing Advice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnjar7/dell_mobile_workstation_purchasing_advice/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnjar7/dell_mobile_workstation_purchasing_advice/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T10:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
 I may choose a Dell Mobile Workstation for work. Does anyone have any experience?
 There are two for me to choose from:
 Dell Precision 3570
 Dell Precision 3571
 According to the following ranking, the 3570's processor is ranked 47th and the 3571's is ranked 1st, but the 3570 has 16GB more RAM (for a total of 32GB). 
 I use the Dell 27" S2721DGFA monitor twice. The 3571's graphics card is slightly better than the 3570's according to the following ranking.
 No special programs are used. Office, browser, a few VPN clients, anti-virus software, vulnerability scans. I work a lot in the browser. Important for me is a good performance. That's it. 
 My questions:
 Which one is better for very fast and reliable "office" work?
 What are the differences between the two?
 Or is it worthwhile to put one together yourself? That would look like this. However, I can't find anything about the integrated Intel graphics card GT2 and I don't know if it can handle two 27" monitors.
 I am very much looking forward to your feedback and thank you in advance. :)
    submitted by    /u/Melodramatisch  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[docs.microsoft.com is now learn.microsoft.com]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnia73/docsmicrosoftcom_is_now_learnmicrosoftcom/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnia73/docsmicrosoftcom_is_now_learnmicrosoftcom/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T09:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft have rearranged things, again.
 So if you use site: in your google searches remember to change what you have been used to.
 And any some handy bookmarks you had from before will now give you a 404 page. But at least the 404 page usually gives you a link to the new location. Some old links, but not all, do redirect.
 EDIT: changed bookmark stuff based on u/lanathell's feedback.
    submitted by    /u/ZAFJB  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Win Server 2016 - local admin gets operation cancelled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xni5al/win_server_2016_local_admin_gets_operation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xni5al/win_server_2016_local_admin_gets_operation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T08:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there, apologies if this is not the way to submit here. In our environment (mostly server 2012 r2 and 2016) we have a server that is used by a third party company to run reports. For this they require local admin access. About 6 weeks ago, three of these accounts stopped being able to launch most apps, all except for windows accessories and office 365 apps (fat)
 These users are members of the local admins group, they are also part of an ad group that is also in local admins. Launching any other application gives the error ‘this operation has been cancelled due to restrictions in effect on this computer’
 These accounts are only a problem with this server, it’s the only one they would normally access
 I’ve cleared down the local accounts from there, including the registry. I’ve also just created the default app locker execution rules in group policy. These accounts have full unrestricted access to the server but still can’t launch other applications and services. Unfortunately this includes CMD, so even running a gpresult is proving difficult. Anyone had a similar issue?
    submitted by    /u/jeggy111  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. China Cold War | 9.25.22]]></title>
        <id>fef8ee00-f8d7-4fa9-af8c-a571d4d4e4db</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts have warned that the U-S and China are engaged in a cold war,  warning that the communist nation of a billion people is more intent than ever on supplanting the United States as the dominant superpower on the world stage. And they’re getting more brazen in their efforts.  On this Sunday episode of Morning Wire, we look into the growing threat of China abroad and here at home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[access review of CEO accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnhlb9/access_review_of_ceo_accounts/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnhlb9/access_review_of_ceo_accounts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T08:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! I would like to know how you everyone here handles account reviews for VIP employees (in our case CEO). 
 We have to do a review of all accesses in applications in anticipation of an audit. We now take a report of each user and their access. Their managers review the access and tell us if some changes are needed. But the CEO has access to a few applications and we are not sure who should review his access. Someone at the Board? In AD he does not have a anyone set as the Manager.
    submitted by    /u/scallopedsambar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated Microsoft 365 updates overview?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xngqmk/automated_microsoft_365_updates_overview/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xngqmk/automated_microsoft_365_updates_overview/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T07:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I work with Microsoft products like Azure, inTune, Dynamics and other 365 products to implement modern workplace solutions for our end users. 
 I find it sometimes difficult to have an overview of all future updates and end of life products that are being pushed by Microsoft. It would be nice to have this automated in some way.
 How do you guys manage this?
    submitted by    /u/max25k  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMWare and Windows Server Patching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnf86u/vmware_and_windows_server_patching/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnf86u/vmware_and_windows_server_patching/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T06:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all
 I started new job, where I will need to do windows server, Azure Vm and VMware host patching
 there are very few servers no WSUS employed or anything else, because they will go away sooner or later 
 my manager asked me about my plan to patch those servers/hosts 
 they are mixes of dev and production 
 I am thinking:
 -Update windows servers when update released (every month) and when critical update is been pushed 
 -Create snapshot for VM before update (is this necessary?)
 -Update VMware server software when new update is released (minor updates for the same version)
 -Update the production servers off hours 
 -Test updates (by running the application and testing all functions)
 -Rollback update if test went wrong
 -For Switches, update one switch after making copy from configurations with old FW
 -Test the switches and be ready to rollback to backup file
 ​
 ​
 is there any ideas or things I need to add to the plan?
 ​
 thanks in advanced
    submitted by    /u/Sa77if  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How are you in SMBs doing VPN for remote users/vendors?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnbjkq/how_are_you_in_smbs_doing_vpn_for_remote/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnbjkq/how_are_you_in_smbs_doing_vpn_for_remote/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T02:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I still rock an old ass RRAS VPN on 2003 VM, obviously it has got to go... with that I have few choices, I can pay more for the already expensive barracuda firewalls to I believe give me a decent VPN client + single sign-on, I'm not sure how I would do 2FA with that but I assume it can do that as it has enough bells & whistles to confuse me anytime I look at it. I also don't look forward to deploying the client to my users, I love built-in windows VPN and it always treated me well.
 OR
 just a new 2019 VM with VPN and somehow enable 2FA on that. 
 OR
 the VM + I wouldn't mind paying for DUO or something similar either, just not sure how that works to be honest with windows VPN server? can it? 
 what say you /r/sysadmin?
    submitted by    /u/Unlucky_Strawberry90  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uptick In Spam DocuSign emails - is this a new malware delivery attack vector?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnbece/uptick_in_spam_docusign_emails_is_this_a_new/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xnbece/uptick_in_spam_docusign_emails_is_this_a_new/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T02:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have seen a rash of bogus emails getting through our filters because its being delivered by DocuSign's legitimate service/address *.docusign.com, *.docusign.net however the sender will be for example "Chase Bank" with a sender email in the body [00014745billing@outlook.com](mailto:00014745billing@outlook.com). Our users are opening them because they trust the DocuSign domain. The few I have investigated redirected to a 365 sign in when you click "review document" or to a static file with an incoherent message that I presume they are trying to get you to download. So I am assuming malware delivery and credential harvesting. All I can say is thank god for MFA and poorly designed fake documents. However I worry its going to hit the right person where the fake document makes sense, like a plausible contract, and the user actually downloads and opens. 
 Besides education is there a better way to lock this down other then blocking DocuSign and having to manually release.
    submitted by    /u/AwayAd9297  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fully remote means REALLY fully remote, where should I move if I could move anywhere?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xn6rpn/fully_remote_means_really_fully_remote_where/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xn6rpn/fully_remote_means_really_fully_remote_where/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T23:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My employer has a presence in most major countries and is very encouraging of sponsoring its remote employees to move wherever they feel suits them best (with an adjustment in pay depending on the destination). 
 I'm in the US currently and while I've got great health insurance, I'd love to find somewhere with a sane healthcare system. Having lived somewhere with harsh winters, I'd prefer not to deal with those anymore. I unfortunately only speak English and have not had luck picking up other languages.
 If you could move somewhere warm and english-speaking-friendly, where would you go?
    submitted by    /u/lorimar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Found my company has a public facing website that doesn't need a password to log in. Not sure where to proceed.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xn2jkf/found_my_company_has_a_public_facing_website_that/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xn2jkf/found_my_company_has_a_public_facing_website_that/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T20:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long story short, it's a website meant for employees. But the public internet can access it as well.
 The problem is that they rolled out a update a few months ago where users don't need to enter in a password to log in. I discovered this by accident.
 You just need the username, and the system will log you into the account, giving you information such as the employee's addresses, contact information, payroll information and so on. Nor is there a "too many attempts" timeout, because I presume that was tied with the password.
 IT department at my office has no idea who to contact to address that issue.
 The website's own contact email is never answered. When I called them and waited +3 hours on the line, the help desk person insisted that removing the password was a convince feature, not a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My wife vetoed my plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8dEIy1YXJ4A</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8dEIy1YXJ4A"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T16:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SD-WAN Functionality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmvddb/sdwan_functionality/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmvddb/sdwan_functionality/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T15:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all - I'm trying to verify that our Meraki SD-WAN is actually utilizing the full bandwidth of our 2 500mb circuits and not seeing what I thought I would, so hoping for a suggestion. Doing an internet speed test yields the same result if I take one of the circuits out (approx 500mb up/down). The MX device shows that both circuits are active and it is set to load balance. That said, the device still makes you pick a 'primary' circuit and seems to be using that one exclusively for my testing.
    submitted by    /u/bmessinachicago  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fully remote means I can live anywhere, should I move?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xmsyf2/fully_remote_means_i_can_live_anywhere_should_i/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xmsyf2/fully_remote_means_i_can_live_anywhere_should_i/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T13:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying for a fully remote position which lead me to thinking, I can live anywhere now (assuming I get it). I could live at the beach, on a mountain, in the city, on a farm... Anyone dealt with this before? Did you move? I would love to lay low for a few years and save cash, but don't know if I would dig living in a small town. Just looking for opinions.
 EDIT: I would not be leaving the country or even my state. Just meant changing cities. I live in NC, so I could live at the beach, or the mountains, or stay in Raleigh, or move out into the sticks.
    submitted by    /u/paperlevel  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overmedicating our Children? | 9.24.22]]></title>
        <id>ece4e5f1-4eea-4db1-9c5f-23e0e688ec20</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A record number of teens are being prescribed psychiatric drugs, concerns rise about the state of the global food supply, and an interview with Whole Foods founder John Mackey. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are there devices that negotiate POE with a POE-Switch resulting in passive POE - but not having a separate power source (so no POE Injector)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xml8ii/are_there_devices_that_negotiate_poe_with_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xml8ii/are_there_devices_that_negotiate_poe_with_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a POE+ Switch, that specifically states no passive POE is possible. Are there devices allowing passive POE that draw power from this switch?
 I am aware there are POE injectors, I have them. But are there devices that negotiate POE with the POE-Switch itself and drawing power from the switch and not from a separate power source?
    submitted by    /u/greyish_sea  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding macs from Vxlan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmkwey/finding_macs_from_vxlan/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmkwey/finding_macs_from_vxlan/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T06:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I work in a juniper dominant environment and Vxlan plays a big role. Chasing down a mac/ip address is fairly simple but not here. Does anyone know how with junos to chase down a mac/ip address once "show arp" or "show ethernet-switching table" gives the output of a lsi or vtep interface on the interface column?
    submitted by    /u/300betos  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA Thinks You're RICH - WAN Show September 23, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7YuiFlhe8j4</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7YuiFlhe8j4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T03:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connection Stapling?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmc977/connection_stapling/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmc977/connection_stapling/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T23:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there, I stumbled upon a P2P cli file transfer software named croc (https://github.com/schollz/croc), however there is some terminology in the read-me I couldn't quite understand.
 Under the Self-Host Relay section it says:
  
The relay is needed to staple the parallel incoming and outgoing connections.
  
Now I did find articles on OCSP Stapling but this doesn't seem to apply here (correct me if I'm wrong). In a blog post the creator, when talking about how croc works, explains:
  
There are better ways than sequentially uploading and downloading. Instead, you can use a relay server to create a full-duplex real-time communication layer between the two computers so that “uploading” and “downloading” occur simultaneously between the two computers.
  
Which in context sounds a lot like NAT hole punching. Is this just a misuse of the term stapling or is stapling something completely different / nonsense? Thanks in advance!
    submitted by    /u/Apocryphenn  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[when to use fiber?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmaoe7/when_to_use_fiber/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xmaoe7/when_to_use_fiber/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T22:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of a company that has a main server then several departments that are connected via multiple switches and maybe 200m of ethernet cable. Each department has maybe 10-15 computers and multiple machines connected . The networking was done here and there and with different types of cable over the past 10 years. Now things are running slow in one of the departments. We planned to run a new cat6 cable (100m) directly to the main switch. Is it worth it? Is it better to have a fiber cable with a converter on each end between two switches? The main use is transfering small files between computers/machines but during peak hours when most people are connected to the network, stuff stops working well and connections get interrupted
    submitted by    /u/fish85963  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday Afternoon Update | 9.23.22]]></title>
        <id>3b2ca028-d74a-4f99-a07e-14b4339f9189</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Central Podcast LIVE | Episode 285 | September 23rd 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6Gr4_EOXxT4</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6Gr4_EOXxT4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T19:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Windows Central</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IP Redundancy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm6hin/ip_redundancy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm6hin/ip_redundancy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T19:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[​
 I have queries regarding the redundancy issue (cisco).
 Scenario: End Customer has Primary-backup set up. I have checked the configuration and found no redundancy protocol is used in it. (sh vrrp , sh glbp, sh standy have no results) .
 My Query
 1) Could the router have redundancy even if the above protocol is not used? (Is it thru the access list? route-map configuration ??)
 2) How to check if both routers are redundant?
 3) if Back to back access is unavailable, Could someone help with the configuration? (no physical cable is connected between both the device to get access to primary via backup or vice versa)
    submitted by    /u/Vegetable_Depth_4196  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to assign a DHCP pool to a VLAN (Cisco) ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm4gul/how_to_assign_a_dhcp_pool_to_a_vlan_cisco/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm4gul/how_to_assign_a_dhcp_pool_to_a_vlan_cisco/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T17:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a university project, I built a network of 4 interconnected CISCO switches (2960), with one of them connected to a single router.
 I've defined DCHP pools on the router, and created five VLANs on the switches (using VTP) based on ports. I'm now trying to assign each DCHP pool to a VLAN, but I can't find a solution to do so.
 For example, a user connecting on the port 1 (VLAN 1) would get an IP in the DHCP pool named "VLAN1".
 Do you have any idea on how I could implement that on these switch?
 Thanks :)
    submitted by    /u/lulucmy  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Engineer in the Quant/HFT Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm4cv0/network_engineer_in_the_quanthft_industry/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm4cv0/network_engineer_in_the_quanthft_industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T17:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bit of background about myself:
  
I'm a high school student, soon to graduate.
 I've had an interest in Network Engineering for about two years.
 I've developed knowledge in BGP (RPKI filtering & MP-BGP), OSPF (multi-area & summarisation), VPNs (WG & IPsec) and some Network Automation (Python OOP stuff & Drone CI/CD).
 Have picked up some Docker and Linux stuff as well.
  
I'm starting an internship at a High Frequency Trading Firm in London, with their network team. It's likely that they will give me a return offer.
 I've looked into HFT networks and found that multicast is used a lot (to receive market data from exchanges). I'm planning to set up a multicast IPTV server and run some packet captures to become more familiar with it. Also, I've read whitepapers on the switching platforms that the firm uses.
 Is there anything major to HFT networks I'm missing?
 I hope this doesn't break rule #5, I thought that r/networking would be the best place to ask about such a niche industry.
 Thanks
    submitted by    /u/--Fatal--  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In My Dreams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm0ez6/in_my_dreams/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xm0ez6/in_my_dreams/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T15:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone else ever solve complex network issues or design stuff in your dreams? I know it sounds crazy but I sometimes go to sleep thinking about an issue and solve it in my sleep.
    submitted by    /u/Ok_Insect_600  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mystery IP on server]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlvfgt/mystery_ip_on_server/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlvfgt/mystery_ip_on_server/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T11:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have this old windows 2012 server (I know, I know), it is configured and responding to an IP on the 10.8.1.x subnet, it is attached to a Cisco switch via cat 5e. It has several nics but only one active (not disabled). The server isn't set up with any virtualization. The issue is that the switch is showing 2 Mac addresses coming in on the same port that the server is attached to, arp shows another IP address , associated with a Mac address that is sequentially 1 higher (last digit) than the configured nic on the server, it also has an IP address in the same subnet as the one configured on the server so it would appear as though it would possibly be a secondary port on the nic. The server responds to pings on this secondary IP, nmap scans show only udp 68 being open on this IP. Here is the weird part, the machine doesn't show the IP being configured anywhere, ipconfig doesn't even list the Mac nor the IP of this secondary IP. Running Wireshark while pinging the secondary IP shows what you would expect from a configured nic, except it isn't configured anywhere that I can find...any suggestions on locating where this is coming from would be greatly appreciated.
    submitted by    /u/judgethisyounutball  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday's Promotional Thread - September 23, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xlud45/fridays_promotional_thread_september_23_2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xlud45/fridays_promotional_thread_september_23_2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T11:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a great deal of content out there that violates our advertising/promotion rule, from scripts and software to tutorials and videos. We have received a number of requests for exemptions to the rule, and rather than allowing the front page to get consumed, we thought we'd try a weekly thread that allows for that kind of content. We don't have a catchy name for it yet, so please let us know if you have any ideas!
 In this thread, feel free to show us your pet project, YouTube videos, blog posts, or whatever else you may have and share it with the community. Commercial advertisements, affiliate links, or links that appear to be monetization-grabs will still be removed.
    submitted by    /u/AutoModerator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new Microsoft Surface event has been confirmed! 👀]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HT0jOtIprLY</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HT0jOtIprLY"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T09:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Windows Central</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does any smartphone read every bit of information that passes through it (radiowaves) and ignores those ones which it cannot decrypt? Or is there a header of some kind in every packet of data which says "this is for you"?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlt1x1/does_any_smartphone_read_every_bit_of_information/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlt1x1/does_any_smartphone_read_every_bit_of_information/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T09:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's imagine three wifi routers close to each other. Two of them (wifi1, wifi2) works on the same channel; the other one (wifi3) works on the channel that overlaps with those two. And let's say I have two smartphones (s1, s2), both of them connected to wifi1. When I download something or just scroll through my feed with s1, how do I distinguish those signals that are intended for me if: 
 1) s2 is also downloading
 2) wifi2 and wifi3 works on the same frequency as the wifi1 and other users are also downloading something using those two wifi.
    submitted by    /u/Glum-Description-582  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terrorists at the Border | 9.23.22]]></title>
        <id>3e1281e5-8364-4642-b61c-72e0bfe310cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A record number of criminals are entering the US at our southern border, a former Google executive warns of China’s technology hegemony, and the elections that will determine who will control the House and the Senate. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are there any decent network modeling software and simulation software out there?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xliqbp/are_there_any_decent_network_modeling_software/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xliqbp/are_there_any_decent_network_modeling_software/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've been given a relatively simple task at work but there doesn't seem to be a software out there that seems to be able to achieve this and I'm scratching my head out.
 Essentially we want to build an IoT environment using MQTT as the message protocol. We want to model this environment and simulate the message flow & bandwidth utilization. It's a simple publisher > broker > multiple subscribers chain. 
 Our aim is to play around with the values and perform certain what-if scenarios. (e.g if there's a message spike, can the bandwidth manage? How long would it take for all my subscribers to receive the payload?) 
 Is there a easy modeling tool that is able to do this? A simple system A sending data to system B. I can vary the bandwidth, payload size and frequency and output the bandwidth utilization
    submitted by    /u/butilikewaffles  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogpost Friday!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlhm4v/blogpost_friday/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlhm4v/blogpost_friday/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T00:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Read-only Friday! It is time to put your feet up, pour a nice dram and look through some of our member's new and shiny blog posts.
 Feel free to submit your blog post and as well a nice description to this thread.
 Note: This post is created at 00:00 UTC. It may not be Friday where you are in the world, no need to comment on it.
    submitted by    /u/AutoModerator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you write and store your own personal docs/notes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlf25a/how_do_you_write_and_store_your_own_personal/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlf25a/how_do_you_write_and_store_your_own_personal/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've been using OneNote for my own personal IT notes, specifically networking stuff. If I get shown how to do something, I write up the process. Same if I figure something out for myself, etc. Over 3-4 jobs now I've carried the same OneNote file with me and added to it, but I'm falling out of love with OneNote.
 I was thinking about an alternative like Evernote, but it doesn't seem to have the same simplicity that OneNote has, sadly. If I could import my notes without having to copy-paste everything, I'd certainly give Evernote a try, but I like to have things organised under tabs (Network, Security, VMware, Wifi, etc) and have my various pages categorised that way. I'd also need to figure out if Evernote can do this too.
 What do you use for your personal notetaking? What does it do that you like? What does it do that you don't like? Thanks for any input to the discussion.
    submitted by    /u/MotorTentacle  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't know how I got thrown into governance for a network device manufacturer, but here I am...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlcz4c/dont_know_how_i_got_thrown_into_governance_for_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlcz4c/dont_know_how_i_got_thrown_into_governance_for_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T20:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My title is DevOps/Infrastructure engineer at a startup network device manufacturer which is a subset of a very large company. We have a lot of freedom but I foresee things like security, accounting, that sort of thing coming down the line but all I know these are nebulous, untimed goals. 
 The development network where all of our stuff lives has been described as the "wild wild west" by my boss who wants a "map" of where everything is. That so far is a few hundred connected devices (laptops, a few routers, smart and dumb switches, etc) in a few workshops, all eventually connected through a main D-Link DGS-1510 switch in a "NOC" so to speak, which is a few dashboards for our deployed production devices routed through the Internet through a MikroTik router. Nothing is ever static, that is t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VLOG Thursday 296: Quad9, SaaSlio, FIDO2, Air Quality, Errata, and Q&A]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zbpwehaSIzM</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zbpwehaSIzM"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T20:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday Afternoon Update | 9.22.22]]></title>
        <id>fb9113cc-db3e-4d30-a373-08258366ebba</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCP hangs on the very last packet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlbbfk/tcp_hangs_on_the_very_last_packet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlbbfk/tcp_hangs_on_the_very_last_packet/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T19:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a damn long time since I've had to dive this deep into a pcap to try and solve an issue, but I'm running out of things to check.
 Client uses a service running on their server to monitor a folder and upload documents to a server over HTTPS.
 Pcap shows handshake looks good, TLS session is negotiated without issue, but once the actual file upload starts, things stop working right. The client will typically send 2-3 packets for any given chunk, but the server only ACKs the first packet. The client then retransmits the next two packets and then gets an ACK for each. So far so good - a bit messy, but at least traffic is flowing.
 Then we get to the very last packet - on the last packet of the session, we end up waiting for 35-40 seconds before we finally get an ACK from the server an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSTP switches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlaan4/rstp_switches/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xlaan4/rstp_switches/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T19:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDIT:UPDATE-my question was answered and pointed in a better direction. Turns out I should have probably posted in a industrial automation sub. Thanks for the info. 
 Are there switches on the market that support RSTP with multiple rings in a switch. I am a design engineer for a BAS manufacturer and the industry is migrating out of rs485 twisted pair to using RSTP compatible switches with a Ring topology to keep costs low on the networking side. For example do switches allow you to set a root and backup port for multiple rings or are you limited to one failover port per switch. I imagine there are a wide range of options based on cost but this would be in the area of 3-5 rings per switch at most for very large networks. 
 To clarify the end goal is to move into An IP friendly physical layer that maintains the cost effectiveness of daisy chains while using ring topology to give a fail over route if the cable is ever damaged/or enough nodes fail we exceed 100m between devices that are online. 
 The current direction looks like a small 8 port industrial switch per network but I grow curious if there could be cost benefit to a single switch 18/24/48 port that could have multiple networks on 1.
    submitted by    /u/Knoon1148  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone said this was impossible]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3CDOSj8fZA4</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3CDOSj8fZA4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T18:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redundant Firewalls to guarantee "basic" internet access in a work environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xl75wv/redundant_firewalls_to_guarantee_basic_internet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xl75wv/redundant_firewalls_to_guarantee_basic_internet/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T17:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just going to throw out a design question here. Recent internet access disasters have us rethinking our internet access methods. Has anyone ever tried to setup two different brands of Firewall brands. One hot and running. Another offline but ready to connect if the first firewall decides to stop working. I know the devil is in the details as far as setting this up but I was wondering if anyone has attempted this.
    submitted by    /u/ethmass  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How FIDO2 Works And Would It Stop MFA Fatigue Attacks?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_E2LZK-bFk</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_E2LZK-bFk"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T17:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper's MX204 - Is the 400gbps of throughput realistic?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xl627v/junipers_mx204_is_the_400gbps_of_throughput/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xl627v/junipers_mx204_is_the_400gbps_of_throughput/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have no experience with Juniper's MX204, but we are considering becoming a Juniper house.
 The platform advertises an impressive 400gbps of throughput but doesn't give any background on where that number comes from. 
 In a layer 3 forwarding application are we really to expect 400gbps of throughput? Does anyone know what the realistic numbers might look like?
    submitted by    /u/Wyattwic  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Your Phishing Training With Phin Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WA4C7yRarcA</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WA4C7yRarcA"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T16:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Absurd Logistics of Concert Tours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MY8AB1wYOtg</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MY8AB1wYOtg"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Wendover Productions</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Different DHCP reservations per subnet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xl255g/different_dhcp_reservations_per_subnet/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xl255g/different_dhcp_reservations_per_subnet/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All, We have a situation where a mobile system moves across multiple subnets across a facility (one facility, multiple subnets). Is it possible to have a dhcp reservation for each of the subnets that it connects to?
    submitted by    /u/sftbnwh_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AA22-265A: Control System Defense: Know the Opponent]]></title>
        <id>17997 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/alerts/aa22-265a"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T12:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: September 22, 2022
Summary
Traditional approaches to securing OT/ICS do not adequately address current threats. 
Operational technology/industrial control system (OT/ICS) assets that operate, control, and monitor day-to-day critical infrastructure and industrial processes continue to be an attractive target for malicious cyber actors. These cyber actors, including advanced persistent threat (APT) groups, target OT/ICS assets to achieve political gains, economic advantages, or destructive effects. Because OT/ICS systems manage physical operational processes, cyber actors’ operations could result in physical consequences, including loss of life, property damage, and disruption of National Critical Functions.
OT/ICS devices and designs are publicly available, often inco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubleshoot strange behaviour when SSH'ing into Cisco Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xkwhul/troubleshoot_strange_behaviour_when_sshing_into/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xkwhul/troubleshoot_strange_behaviour_when_sshing_into/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T09:21:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey Folks,
 I have one switch where when I SSH to the device I get username and password prompt. After that the connection closes without any indication why. This behaviour happens in SecureCRT and Putty. Console connections works fine. VTY config below looks ok to me but I'm not sure. Any ideas?
 ​
 ​
 [09-22-2022 09:37:00:885]line con 0
 [09-22-2022 09:37:00:885] privilege level 15
 [09-22-2022 09:37:00:885] login authentication console
 [09-22-2022 09:37:00:885]line vty 0 4
 [09-22-2022 09:37:00:885] session-timeout 15 
 [09-22-2022 09:37:00:885] exec-timeout 15 0
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028] logging synchronous
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028] length 0
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028] transport input ssh
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028]line vty 5 15
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028] session-timeout 15 
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028] exec-timeout 15 0
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028] logging synchronous
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:028] no exec
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:172] transport input ssh
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:172] transport output none
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:172]!
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:172]ntp server 10.49.129.2
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:172]end
 [09-22-2022 09:37:01:172]
    submitted by    /u/keeganb2000  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NY Files Fraud Charges Against Trump | 9.22.22]]></title>
        <id>c151f876-85ab-4765-9f2d-58225bb1cca0</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Attorney General files a civil lawsuit alleging fraud against President Trump, Minneapolis citizens fund private security amid a severe police shortage, and the state of Virginia introduces new school guidance regarding transgenderism. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This 2300ft cable saved us THOUSANDS of dollars... #SHORTS #networking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQbp64JRkdA</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cQbp64JRkdA"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T03:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Sony Suing Quad9?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=63dZ93K4TC8</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=63dZ93K4TC8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T21:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday Afternoon Update | 9.21.22]]></title>
        <id>ba33d349-c5cc-4992-9e56-f601456c0be0</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The MOST Tricked Out Laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tHNQOJ_nsLc</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tHNQOJ_nsLc"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T18:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AA22-264A: Iranian State Actors Conduct Cyber Operations Against the Government of Albania]]></title>
        <id>17991 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/alerts/aa22-264a"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: September 21, 2022 | Last revised: September 23, 2022
Summary
The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) are releasing this joint Cybersecurity Advisory to provide information on recent cyber operations against the Government of Albania in July and September. This advisory provides a timeline of activity observed, from initial access to execution of encryption and wiper attacks. Additional information concerning files used by the actors during their exploitation of and cyber attack against the victim organization is provided in Appendices A and B.
In July 2022, Iranian state cyber actors—identifying as “HomeLand Justice”—launched a destructive cyber attack against the Government of Albania which rendered …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Driven Software Engineering - Computerphile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3aoLV5i1feo</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3aoLV5i1feo"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Computerphile</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Homelab Show Episode 72: KVM,IPMI, iDRAC, PiKVM and Out Of Band Management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VgdwTckl9Ao</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VgdwTckl9Ao"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election Polling & Gender Clinic Controversy | 9.21.22]]></title>
        <id>551cefe7-37ad-4014-bbdc-54e35bb5d992</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less than 50 days to the midterm elections and new polling shows voters’ opinions continue to shift, a new report raises serious questions about a major U.S. hospital’s gender treatment program, and Europe faces a growing energy crisis. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Hope You Have a LOT of Money... RTX 4000 Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3RIp7CwkBeA</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3RIp7CwkBeA"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T04:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rant Wednesday!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xjov49/rant_wednesday/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/networking/comments/xjov49/rant_wednesday/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T00:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Wednesday! Time to get that crap that's been bugging you off your chest! In the interests of spicing things up a bit around here, we're going to try out a Rant Wednesday thread for you all to vent your frustrations. Feel free to vent about vendors, co-workers, price of scotch or anything else network related. 
 There is no guiding question to help stir up some rage-feels, feel free to fire at will, ranting about anything and everything that's been pissing you off or getting on your nerves!
 Note: This post is created at 00:00 UTC. It may not be Wednesday where you are in the world, no need to comment on it.
    submitted by    /u/AutoModerator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Enterprise Networking Design, Support, and Discussion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday's Afternoon Update | 9.20.22]]></title>
        <id>2fc3fdd0-c9c6-4117-88e8-0661fdb06114</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big pfsense Changes Are Coming!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cPRnr2ep04A</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cPRnr2ep04A"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T17:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 2022 Update — Official Release Demo (Version 22H2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dkcd3ATQq1w</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dkcd3ATQq1w"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Windows Central</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Anti-Censorship Law & Biden Interview | 9.20.22]]></title>
        <id>b7428ef3-7307-4a34-87b4-e251ac8f829b</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Texas anti-censorship law gets a critical court win, the White House walks back politically charged comments from the president, and experts warn that San Francisco is heading for a real estate crash. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monday's Afternoon Update | 9.19.22]]></title>
        <id>38ebfd71-c050-4812-b888-3502339a1a09</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Water Cooled Mac Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Ueel1wXnZk</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Ueel1wXnZk"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T17:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Border Bussing Battle & Spiking Interest Rates | 9.19.22]]></title>
        <id>d4c15963-48f1-4a81-b01c-93ee99a411f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The political battle over the border escalates, mortgage rates reach highest levels since the 2008 Recession, and key races tighten in the usually reliably blue state of New York. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Made a Mistake...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bxya-divayE</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bxya-divayE"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T16:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did the Big Bang Happen? | 9.18.22]]></title>
        <id>6500d92a-4f70-452b-852c-9c63cab51aa7</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newly released photos from the James Webb Space Telescope have allowed scientists to view farther into space, and farther into the past, than ever before. The images emerging are raising questions about the origins of our universe. One viral article from independent scientist Eric Lerner made the rounds on social media in recent weeks with its provocative claim that the Big Bang never happened. We speak to UC San Diego Professor of Cosmology Brian Keating about what the images show, and what we can and can’t conclude from them.  Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This almost BROKE me.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oijav9jJjqM</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Oijav9jJjqM"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T16:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Durham Investigation & Campus Racism Claims | 9.17.22]]></title>
        <id>f311a91c-d9e7-4883-b1ec-2c19a1b667d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The special counsel investigation into the origin of the Russian collusion narrative offers new revelations about a key FBI source, controversy erupts in the sports world over a refuted claim of racial heckling at BYU, and Oberlin college is forced to pay millions for smearing a local bakery. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Tech Divorce - WAN Show September 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QADCRdzqOH0</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QADCRdzqOH0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T03:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uber September 2022 Security Incident and Lessons We Can Learn From It ⚠️]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3dhJ3kccbnc</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3dhJ3kccbnc"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrants in Martha’s Vineyard  | 9.16.22]]></title>
        <id>2c932d2f-4f98-4119-96e5-ddefc282685e</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clashes over illegal immigration between border states and the Biden Administration continue as now Florida begins shipping migrants to sanctuary cities, a third of San Francisco residents say they’re considering moving out, and Phoenix, Arizona is battling a homeless problem that is only getting worse. Get the facts first on Morning Wire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Screwdriver Drop Test! #SHORTS #screwdriver]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0bvZ70wgZVM</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0bvZ70wgZVM"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T01:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VLOG Thursday 295: Quad9, DattoCon, MSPGeek, Errata, and Q&A]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TwFkfdrCiiQ</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TwFkfdrCiiQ"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T20:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday's Afternoon Update | 9.15.22]]></title>
        <id>593a8d3f-dae4-4277-b8c8-1916775d0643</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Prepper PC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nFDBxBUfE74</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nFDBxBUfE74"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Microsoft Teams Store Auth Tokens as Cleartext?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k6tUTVsTN58</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k6tUTVsTN58"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The White Collar Recession | 9.15.22]]></title>
        <id>4da1430e-9494-4c5a-89f9-5e81236717ec</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big banks, tech and real estate companies are cutting staff at a concerning rate, a new investigation finds that the nation’s top medical schools are prioritizing DEI attitudes when screening applicants, and the Biden Administration is met with pushback over proposed changes to Title 9 rules adding gender identity. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday's Afternoon Update | 9.14.22]]></title>
        <id>345a6049-5441-4df6-a7bb-7b91d4720111</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T19:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is So Embarrassing!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AOdp09SYhCc</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AOdp09SYhCc"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T17:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Homelab Show Episode 71 - Retro Homelab]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K34tC0D4XnI</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K34tC0D4XnI"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T16:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AA22-257A: Iranian Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps-Affiliated Cyber Actors Exploiting Vulnerabilities for Data Extortion and Disk Encryption for Ransom Operations]]></title>
        <id>17966 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/alerts/aa22-257a"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: September 14, 2022
Summary
Actions to take today to protect against ransom operations:
known exploited vulnerabilities.
This joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) is the result of an analytic effort among the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), the National Security Agency (NSA), U.S. Cyber Command (USCC) - Cyber National Mission Force (CNMF), the Department of the Treasury (Treasury), the Australian Cyber Security Centre (ACSC), the Canadian Centre for Cyber Security (CCCS), and the United Kingdom’s National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) to highlight continued malicious cyber activity by advanced persistent threat (APT) actors that the authoring agencies assess are affiliated with the Iranian Government’s I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising Inflation & DOJ Subpoenas | 9.14.22]]></title>
        <id>8db652a3-7c44-4dc9-99dd-92e16f8501fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising inflation stuns economists and leads to massive stock market decline, the Justice Department expands January 6th inquiry, and a Twitter whistleblower testifies in Congress. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday’s Afternoon Update | 09.13.22]]></title>
        <id>33efd54e-5982-4ac3-872f-e45116d5f05f</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T21:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing stories you need to know just in time for your drive home. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alternative Uses for Blockchain - Computerphile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qBAOsB6ETrY</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qBAOsB6ETrY"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T17:48:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Computerphile</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This $69 Gaming PC is INCREDIBLE]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xTAzwKiQ7Ns</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xTAzwKiQ7Ns"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Linus Tech Tips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gun Sale Tracking & Rail Worker Strike  | 9.13.22]]></title>
        <id>ce5459eb-48f4-4594-a9e2-4773465c822a</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major credit card companies have announced a new merchant category code that will track the sale of guns and ammunition, a potential strike among U.S. rail workers further threatens the supply chain, and a fraud investigation and home robbery have made the LA mayor’s race national news. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patch Tuesday Megathread (2022-09-13)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xcxdss/patch_tuesday_megathread_20220913/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sysadmin/comments/xcxdss/patch_tuesday_megathread_20220913/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T04:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello r/sysadmin, I'm /u/AutoModerator, and welcome to this month's Patch Megathread!
 This is the (mostly) safe location to talk about the latest patches, updates, and releases. We put this thread into place to help gather all the information about this month's updates: What is fixed, what broke, what got released and should have been caught in QA, etc. We do this both to keep clutter out of the subreddit, and provide you, the dear reader, a singular resource to read.
 For those of you who wish to review prior Megathreads, you can do so here.
 While this thread is timed to coincide with Microsoft's Patch Tuesday, feel free to discuss any patches, updates, and releases, regardless of the company or product. NOTE: This thread is usually posted before the release of Microsoft's updates, which are scheduled to come out at 5:00PM UTC.
 Remember the rules of safe patching:
  
Deploy to a test/dev environment before prod.
 Deploy to a pilot/test group before the whole org.
 Have a plan to roll back if something doesn't work.
 Test, test, and test!
  
   submitted by    /u/AutoModerator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sysadmin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saasilo: Uncover, Manage, and Secure Your Clients’ SaaS ecosystems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=niX7_3P0AAo</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=niX7_3P0AAo"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Border At Breaking Point & Russia-China Alliance Grows | 9.12.22]]></title>
        <id>37fe95a5-241e-4e10-abbd-280935433666</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal authorities released hundreds of migrants into El Paso as the border crisis reaches a breaking point, the growing alliance between Russia and China poses a significant threat to the U.S., and the U.N.’s atomic watchdog reveals alarming developments with Iran’s nuclear program. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Afghan Allies Left Behind | 9.11.22]]></title>
        <id>058dbf3f-bc2e-415a-90c5-467035230cfe</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over a year after the U.S. withdrew from Afghanistan, thousands of American allies remain there – hunted daily by the Taliban, with little hope of escaping the war torn country. We speak with retired Green Beret Scott Mann who founded task force pineapple, a volunteer group that collaborates with the U.S. military in keeping U.S. allies out of harm's way. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Command Execution pfsense pfblocker ⚠️CVE2022-31814]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CmmvOyP4Er8</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CmmvOyP4Er8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T19:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s War in Ukraine & Global Drought Threats | 9.10.22]]></title>
        <id>437a1b73-cdae-4bb5-b81d-4822f0f156b6</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-10T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s war on Ukraine continues to grind on, droughts in several regions are having a massive impact worldwide, and tensions continue to escalate between the U.S. and China over Taiwan. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Queen Elizabeth II | 9.9.22]]></title>
        <id>067d7ffe-1abe-4236-8b15-db4b1d1b2129</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Queen Elizabeth II passes away at age 96, the Biden administration’s handling of oil and gas leases comes under intense scrutiny, and a California teachers union is accused of conducting oppo research on parents who sought to reopen schools. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VLOG Thursday 294: Ryzen XCP-NG Server, What Really Needs To Be Secured,Errata, and Q&A]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SFdWasOXtPo</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SFdWasOXtPo"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T20:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State of the U.S. Economy & New Twitter Controversy | 9.8.22]]></title>
        <id>389368b6-303c-4b13-97c4-23d49155d462</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economy gets both good and bad news, a recent report details Twitter’s attempt to monetize porn on the platform, and the Biden administration’s expansion of student loan forgiveness for government workers pays out billions of dollars. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Homelab Show Episode 70:Questions & Answers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-ScWVCjl0SY</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-ScWVCjl0SY"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money’s Mostly Digital, So Why Is Moving It So Hard?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8xzINLykprA</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8xzINLykprA"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T14:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Wendover Productions</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Graphs - Computerphile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PZBm7M0HGzw</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PZBm7M0HGzw"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T13:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Computerphile</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marriage Equality & Human Rights Abuse in China  | 9.7.22]]></title>
        <id>43126ec2-fd77-4cb3-83b4-994ca22c3fa3</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senate Democrats consider linking marriage equality legislation to a resolution that keeps the government funded, millions of renters face eviction in the near future, and the U.N. releases an eye-opening report detailing severe human rights violations in China’s Xinjiang province. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AA22-249A: #StopRansomware: Vice Society]]></title>
        <id>17941 at https://us-cert.cisa.gov</id>
        <link href="https://us-cert.cisa.gov/ncas/alerts/aa22-249a"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original release date: September 6, 2022 | Last revised: September 8, 2022
Summary
Actions to take today to mitigate cyber threats from ransomware:
known exploited vulnerabilities.
Note: This joint Cybersecurity Advisory (CSA) is part of an ongoing #StopRansomware effort to publish advisories for network defenders that detail various ransomware variants and ransomware threat actors. These #StopRansomware advisories include recently and historically observed tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) and indicators of compromise (IOCs) to help organizations protect against ransomware. Visit stopransomware.gov to see all #StopRansomware advisories and to learn more about other ransomware threats and no-cost resources.
The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the Cybersecurity and Infrastru…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CISA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Grants Trump Special Master Request | 9.6.22]]></title>
        <id>30719bfa-66ef-476a-8beb-cc72cfa2687f</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal judge grants Trump’s request for a special master, Russia closes the largest natural gas pipeline to Europe, and experts say a housing recession has begun. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Holds Rally In PA & Senate Races Tighten | 9.5.22]]></title>
        <id>881284ba-5557-4427-a760-c1dc46d275ae</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former President Trump swipes back at President Biden in Pennsylvania rally, swing state senate races tighten, and national security experts sound the alarm over the administration’s Iran nuclear deal talks. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look Back at Pandemic Response | 9.4.22]]></title>
        <id>715c6c8e-a946-4409-9a52-6e9b44824a68</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Dr. Anthony Fauci gets ready to retire, We take a look back at where the U.S. went wrong in regards to pandemic response, and what officials say they’re doing to regain public confidence. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chilean Constitution Vote & UK Energy Prices  | 9.3.22]]></title>
        <id>b4fcc055-ef8b-4cd2-ba9c-228a7968f54c</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chilean citizens prepare for a historic vote that could scrap the country’s constitution, the PGA up’s it’s game in the continued competition against LIV Golf, and energy bills continue to spike across the U.K. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Sounds Alarm Over ‘MAGA Republicans’ | 9.2.22]]></title>
        <id>f5793854-6f11-49b1-bfd8-de710e07077d</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden delivers a prime time address in which he declares ‘MAGA Republicans’ an existential threat to American democracy, western countries reverse course on nuclear energy, and Miami bucks the national trend on its approach to crime. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VLOG Thursday 293: Krebs Ubiquiti, TrueNAS, XCP-NG,  Errata, and Q&A]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oeNzIdt-DLs</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oeNzIdt-DLs"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T21:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ’s Trump Filing & Trans Surgeries Controversy | 9.1.22]]></title>
        <id>3b9cae15-8ab8-487e-aa0c-77639593609f</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A DOJ court filing lays out new details about the federal Trump probe, hospitals are under fire over transgender surgeries, and Cubans flee the communist country for the U.S. at numbers not seen in decades. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SLAM Robot Mapping - Computerphile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-XU54IsG8Vo</id>
        <link href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-XU54IsG8Vo"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T12:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Computerphile</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk vs. Twitter & CA vs. Doctor ‘Disinformation’ | 08.31.22]]></title>
        <id>c146d69c-1af4-4e04-b91a-0fa0da9316f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk opens a new front in his legal battle with Twitter, California moves to punish doctors for “Covid disinformation,” and GOP senators demand details on the FBI’s communication with Facebook. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Vaccine Push & GOP Plans | 8.30.22]]></title>
        <id>3ac28e3e-8a52-4e08-85d4-2bff165f088e</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House plans a push for a new Covid vaccine targeting BA5, Republicans vow to conduct multiple investigations if they gain control of Congress in November, and a crime spike in Los Angeles is affecting even the city’s most popular destinations. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI ‘Disinformation’ Controversy | 8.29.22]]></title>
        <id>4eb528e2-4862-4d4a-a7c9-666a56249da6</id>
        <link href="https://www.dailywire.com/podcasts/morning-wire"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI responds to controversy over social media “disinformation” censorship, California moves to ban the sale of gas-powered cars, and the FBI’s Trump affidavit is released. Get the facts first on Morning Wire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>podcasts@dailywire.com (The Daily Wire)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>